<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!-- Amazonas -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 8/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_BRAZIL_BRONZE_RAM">
			<Text>Riachuelo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_BRAZIL_BRONZE_RAM_HELP">
			<Text>Unit has [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Plague Immunity[ENDCOLOR] and can [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Move after Attacking[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]Unit can attack again if it has [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Killed a Unit[ENDCOLOR] this turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BRAZIL_AMAZONAS">
			<Text>Amazonas</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BRAZIL_AMAZONAS_HELP">
			<Text>An aggressive and powerful naval vessel. Only Brazil may build it.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Is immune to plague effects like Boarding Party and can move after Attacking. This unit restores all its attacks in a turn whenever it kills a unit. Has the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Breacher[ENDCOLOR] Promotion for free.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BRAZIL_AMAZONAS_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Amazonas is a strong and aggressive ship, able to move and attack multiple targets in a single turn if it can deal lethal damage. Use support from ranged attacks and flanking attacks to maximize your killing potential with a single Amazonas.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BRAZIL_AMAZONAS_TEXT">
			<Text>The Amazonas was a large steam frigate serving as the flagship of the Brazilian Navy during the Paraguayan War, the bloodiest conflict in South American history. The hulking warship played a pivotal roll at the Battle of Riachuelo, where a combined artillery and naval brigade of Paraguayans attempted to ambush the Brazilians in the early morning and under the cover of a dense fog. Caught by surprise, the Brazilians were put at a great disadvantage, but rallied and countered the Paraguayans. The Amazonas proved to be the decisive factor, ramming and sinking two ships and disabling a third. At Riachuelo, the Paraguayans navy was badly damaged, putting a halt to their momentum for the remainder of the war. Brazil and its allies took the initiative and maintained naval supremacy for the remainder of the war.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Andelsbevægelse -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius, modified and incorporated by adan_eslavo 10/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE">
			<Text>Andelsbevægelse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when constructing Buildings in this City. 10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food created by the City counts as [ICON_GOLD] Gold Per Turn. The [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Farming[ENDCOLOR] Process is 15% more effective at converting [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and reducing [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Distress.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food to Grass and Plains tiles near the City. +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Nearby Farms and Pastures.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Does not require [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Andelsbevægelse is a Danish unique building which can speed up building production. The building's massive bonuses to growth help your empire to multiply, especially when surrounded by plains and pastures.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DENMARK_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Andelsbevægelse was a Danish Cooperative Movement, corporations where individual members each owned a share in the risks and profits of the collective. Co-ops, as they are commonly referred to, continue to be popular in the farming industry as a way of mitigating bad harvests on the part of a few members.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After the disastrous Second War of Schleswig where Denmark lost considerable territory, Denmark began to reclaim moors in central and western Jutland for farming. Shortly after, the rapidly industrializing United States began pouring exports of grain into Denmark's biggest customer, Great Britain, tanking the prices for Denmark's produce. With the livelihoods of many Danish farmers at risk, they formed a new strategy to switch from grain products to dairy and meat.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This shift in Danish agriculture was full of uncertainty, requiring that farmers form the Andelsbevægelse to share in the risks. By the time prices for grain had finally stabilized, Danish agriculture had completely changed. Dairies and slaughterhouses dotted the landscape; now they were IMPORTING grain from Russia to feed their livestock! 
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Armada -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 8/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_SANTA_MARIA">
			<Text>Santa María</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_SANTA_MARIA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_INVINCIBLE">
			<Text>Invincible</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SPAIN_INVINCIBLE_HELP">
			<Text>+5 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]at full Health[ENDCOLOR]. -1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Moves. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA">
			<Text>Armada</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA_HELP">
			<Text>A Slow, but incredibly dangerous ship. Only the Spanish may build it.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]More expensive than the Corvette it replaces. Gains additional strength when at full HP and generates [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points when it defeats a unit. Begins with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Boarding Party I[ENDCOLOR] promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Armada is a powerful ship in its era. You are unlikely to chase down an enemy, but brilliant maneuvering could force an engagement. Much more imposing when at full health, make sure to make contact with the enemy before they can place ranged attacks, or you will lose a great deal of power in your initial melee combat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_ARMADA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The "Great and Most Fortunate Navy", the Spanish Armada, was a fleet of 130 ships constructed for the invasion of England and the overthrow the tyrannical Reformist, Elizabeth I. The Armada was one of the largest fleets ever seen in Europe, raised at great expense by Philip II in retribution for England's break from the Catholic Church, their execution of Mary, Queen of Scots, their support for the Dutch revolt against Spain, and the illegitimacy of Elizabeth I.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Spanish ships were outnumbered by England’s navy, but they easily outgunned the smaller English vessels. In the end, however, it was not firepower, but speed which won the day, allowing the small English vessels to harry the lumbering Spanish Juggernaut, sinking 10 ships. When finally forced to retire to Spain, a navigational error blew the Armada off-course and onto the Irish coast, where fierce storms dashed the ships against the rocks. When the Armada managed to reach Spain, only 67 of the original 130 ships remained, full of sickly, starving, and demoralized sailors.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The lessons of the Spanish Armada informed naval strategy for the next two centuries. Cannons and ranged action had now overtaken boarding and ramming as the primary methods of attack; sinking, rather than capturing, was now the priority. With this stunning victory, England had wrested naval dominance from Spain, a lead they would maintain until the rise of the United States in WWII.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"I sent the Armada against men, not God's winds and waves".[NEWLINE]
				-Philip II
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Baan Chang -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 6/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG">
			<Text>Elephant Camp</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to all Forests worked by this City. +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith to Camps and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to Lumber Mills near this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 4 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City. Internal [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes from this City generate +4 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in City for every 2 Strategic Resources imported from City-State Allies. +10 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +10 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture whenever a City-State gifts a Unit, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Allows [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to be moved from this City along [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes inside your Civilization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Baan Chang is the Siamese unique replacement for the Workshop. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Workshop, The Baan Chang increases Culture from lumber mills, and gives Faith from Camps. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City-State gifts, both Strategic Resources and Units, provide additional benefits in cities with a Baan Chang, so be sure to make strong alliances to get the most from this building.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIAM_BAAN_CHANG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Often thought of as ceremonial and military implements first, perhaps the greatest contribution of elephants to human society has been as beasts of burden. Elephants are prized as a labour force even in modern times for their ability to haul the dense teak lumber found only in Burma and Thailand. The strength of a fully grown elephant is matched only by its grace, navigating difficult and uneven terrain while carrying heavy loads. With their delicate command of the forest trails, elephants also reduce the potential damage of logging roads to the surrounding forest.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The jobs of Southeast Asia's working elephants have come under threat within the past few decades with the mechanization of logging. Elephants and their mahouts have been forced to look for work in tourism and religious festivals, jobs which elephants find terribly stressful.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Bastu -->
		<!-- Created by pineppledan 25/11/2017, modified and incorporated by adan_eslavo 17/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU">
			<Text>Bastu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Swedish Bad Stuga (bath cabin), or Bastu, is a small cabin designed as a bathing and dry heat spa. A stove or furnace heats the room to 200°F before patrons enter, where they will recline and sweat. Bastus are a social affair, places for discussion and relaxation with family and friends, but were also places for food curing and childbirth in earlier times.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				It is not known where or when Scandinavian sweat baths were first created, but it was well before the Christianization of Scandinavia, as evidenced by their ubiquity throughout medieval Europe. By the time written accounts first described Scandinavian sweat baths, Nordic countries had already created varied and distinct cultures surrounding them.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The health benefits of heat baths are many and varied. Sessions have been shown to relieve cold symptoms and increase pain thresholds. They also help with rheumatic pain and fatigue, and may even reduce the risk of dementia. Prolonged use of a sauna has been linked to reduced male fertility, however, and heat baths should never be enjoyed while under the effects of alcohol.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Swedish replacement for the Baths. In addition to the bonuses of the Baths, the Bastu provides bonuses for lakes and tundra. Science and Culture is generated whenever a citizen is born, and extra Food is generated during Golden Ages. Unlike the Baths, the Bastu does not require a river,</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDEN_BASTU_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to Lake Tiles and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 Tundra Tiles worked. Gain 25% of the [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and 15% of the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture output of the City as an instant boost when a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to Temples, Amphitheaters and Gardens in this City. +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_FOOD] Food in the City during [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE]Golden Ages.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Does not require a River.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Barbican -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BARBICAN">
			<Text>Embrasure</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BARBICAN_HELP">
			<Text>+33% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Range Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Garrison in the City[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN">
			<Text>Barbican</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN_HELP">
			<Text>Replaces the Castle. Gives a Free [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Armory[ENDCOLOR] in the City when built.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Damage from all sources against this City is reduced by 3. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for Quarries worked by this City. 15% [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Military Supply from Population. Contains 1 slot for a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Art or Artifact.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+10% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength for City Bombardment and +33% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength for Ranged units, and Siege Units garrisoned in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_CITY_STATE] Empire Size Modifier is reduced by 5% in this City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Polish replacement for both the Castle and the Armory, but a bit stronger than both. Must have built Walls in the city. In addition to the city defense and unit training bonuses, the ranged attacks of both the city and any Ranged units garrisoned in the city are increased.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLAND_BARBICAN_TEXT">
			<Text>	
				A Barbican is a fortified outpost or archery tower, forming part of a city’s outer defense. The towers were often situated with a clear line of fire towards the city’s gates, and connected to the city walls via a walled road called the ‘neck’. The most famous barbican was built in Kraków in 1499 during the reign of Jan Olbracht. Its construction took inspiration from two other Barbicans in Torun (1429) and Chelm (1449), and was built in response to the danger posed by encroaching Ottoman and Wallachian forces.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Barbicans became obsolete in the 15th century due to improvements in siege tactics and artillery. The Warsaw barbican, erected in 1540, was an anachronism long before it was completed. The tower was used only once by the Swedish in 1656, while trying to prevent Poland from retaking the city. The Swedish had captured the city without a fight two years prior.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Ballista -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_ON_BALLISTA">
			<Text>Legatus Legionis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_ON_BALLISTA_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]if the unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]starts its turn near a Great General[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_EFFECT">
			<Text>Siege Mobility</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_LEGATUS_LEGIONIS_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Banco Giro -->
		<!-- created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VENICE_BANCOGIRO">
			<Text>Banco Giro</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VENICE_BANCOGIRO_HELP">
			<Text>Requires a Market in the City.[NEWLINE]-1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_GOLD] Poverty. When you spend [ICON_GOLD] Gold to purchase Units or invest in Buildings in this City, 15% of the cost is converted into [ICON_RESEARCH] Science. 4% of [ICON_GOLD] Gold in the City is converted into [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Merchant Points each turn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Caravansaries and Customs Houses in the City gain +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. [NEWLINE]Each Banco Giro on Empire provides:[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the Rialto District.[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to the Arsenale di Venezia.[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +2 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism to the Murano Glassworks.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_GOLD] Gold: +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SILVER] Silver: +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_GEMS] Gems: +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VENICE_BANCOGIRO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Banco Giro is a Renaissance-era building, replacing the Bank. In addition to the bonuses of a Bank, each Banco Giro on Empire provides yields to your Murano Glassworks, Rialto District, or Arsenale di Venezia national wonder. Additionally, a percentage of all gold generated in your cities is also given as Great Merchant Points. With the Banco Giro, Venice has a means of generating Merchants of Venice at a much higher rate, as long as you can keep the gold flowing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VENICE_BANCOGIRO_TEXT">
			<Text>The Venetian Banco del Giro, meaning "Bank of Circulation", or simply the Bank of Venice, was founded in 1619 as one of the oldest and longest-running reserve banks in the western world. For centuries prior to the creation of the central banking system, Venice had been at the forefront of accounting and banking innovations, systematizing the double-entry bookkeeping system, and creating the first instance of transferrable public debt. The Banco Giro was established by the Venetian Senate to address the need for an institution that could handle non-cash transfers, as well as to manage the system of emergency loans used by the government. The Banco Giro continued to fulfill this function until the Fall of the Venetian Republic to the French Empire in 1797, when Napoleon dissolved many of Venice's national institutions, including its banking system.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Black Tug -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 29/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MONGOLIA_MINGGHAN">
			<Text>Mingghan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MONGOLIA_MINGGHAN_HELP">
			<Text>+5 XP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR]. +20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if unit is standing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillaged Tile[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG">
			<Text>Black Tug</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG_HELP">
			<Text>Aggressive and menacing Medieval Era Mounted Melee Unit. Only the Mongols may build it. It is stronger against Wounded Units or while standing on Pillaged Tiles. Gains additional XP for pillaging.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Black Tug is a Mongolian unique unit, replacing the Knight. It is stronger and deals more damage to wounded units, and while standing on pillaged tiles. As mounted unit, the Black Tug is vulnerable to Pikemen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOLIA_BLACK_TUG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A tug is a pole with circularly arranged horse tail-hairs of varying colors arranged at the top -- a symbol of the importance of horses in Mongol life. A white-haired banner is used as a peacetime symbol, while the black banner was for wartime. The original white banner disappeared early in history, but the black banner survived as the repository of Genghis Khan's soul. The Mongols continued to honor the banner, building a monastery to guard it, but the tug was eventually lost amidst the Stalinist purges of Mongolian nationalists, monks, and intellectuals in 1937.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Nine White banners of Mongolia were revived after democracy was adopted in the early 1990s, replacing the previous communist flags. The modern Mongolian nine white banners are kept in the Government Palace in Ulaanbaatar; the modern Mongolian black banners are kept in the Ministry of Defense.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	
		<!-- Brauhaus -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan on 26/06/2022 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_BEER_HALL">
			<Text>Bräuhaus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_BEER_HALL_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Through and through, Germany is a beer culture, whose historic and cultural ties to the drink date back to antiquity. With the professionalization and commodification of brewing in the middle ages, beer moved from a private cottage industry into the inns and public houses, which took the form of Brewhouses (Bräuhauser) and Beer Halls (Bierhaller) in Germany. The greatest and most renowned Brewhouses are found in the Free State of Bavaria, where beer halls, beer gardens, and the annual Oktoberfest have become synonymous with Bavarian culture. Especially notable breweries are found throughout Munich, which are all historically subject to the Bavarian Beer Purity Law -- the Reinheitsegebot -- which dictated that the only ingredients that could be used in the production of beer were water, barley and hops. Adopted by the Bavarian state in 1516, the Reinheitsegebot is one of the oldest pieces of food safety legislation still in effect today. Even before the rise of German nationalism, the Reinheitsegebot had inspired similar regulation in nearby kingdoms and its universal adoption was a condition of Bavaria's unification with Germany in 1871.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				As a place where light and food were freely available, the Brewhouses were a cornerstone of public life in southern Germany, acting as the birthplace for numerous revolutionary ideas and movements that gripped Germany in the 18th and 19th centuries. In the wake of the French Revolution, German liberals organized in the Beer Halls of Munich to demand reforms of the monarchy in a series of uprisings from 1848 to 1849. During the 1910s, Vladimir Lenin was a frequent patron of the Munich Hofbräuhaus, where he did much of his political agitations and initial founding of the Bolshevik party, which would go on to form the Soviet Union. Most famous, however, was Adolf Hitler, who announced the formation of his National Socialist (Nazi) Party at the Hofbräuhaus am Platzl in 1920, and was arrested for treason in 1923 after a failed coup d'état at the Bürgerbräukeller. This episode became known as the Beer Hall Putsch, and the resulting trial gave Hitler a national platform to spread his political ideology, leading to his widespread fame and the rise of German fascism.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_BEER_HALL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Bräuhaus is the unique German replacement for the Windmill. In addition to the standard bonuses of a Windmill, the Bräuhaus provides bonuses to Happiness, which grow stronger with the number of policies you have adopted. Each Bräuhaus on Empire provides an instant boost of Culture whenever you gift a Military Unit to a City-State. The Bräuhaus' rewards for policy adoption and unit gifting both get stronger after you adopt an Ideology, with different yield bonuses depending on what Ideology you adopt. Prioritize culture via allying with City-States in order to increase the power of your Bräuhauser.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_BEER_HALL_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when constructing Buildings. Grocers, Granaries, and Nearby [ICON_RES_WHEAT] Wheat, [ICON_RES_MAIZE] Maize, and [ICON_RES_RICE] Rice Resources produce +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Nearby Marshes and Lakes produce +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness for every 9 Policies you have adopted. Gain 10 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in this City whenever you gift a military unit to a City-State, Scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gains additional bonuses after adopting an [COLOR_MAGENTA]Ideology[ENDCOLOR]:[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][ICON_IDEOLOGY_FREEDOM] [COLOR_MAGENTA]Freedom[ENDCOLOR]: Gain 10 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science whenever you adopt a tenet and 10 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points when you gift a Military Unit to a [ICON_CITY_STATE] City-State, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][ICON_IDEOLOGY_ORDER] [COLOR_MAGENTA]Order[ENDCOLOR]: Gain 10 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production whenever you adopt a tenet and 10 [ICON_FOOD] Food when you gift a Military Unit to a [ICON_CITY_STATE] City-State, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][ICON_IDEOLOGY_AUTOCRACY] [COLOR_MAGENTA]Autocracy[ENDCOLOR]: Gain 10 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture whenever you adopt a tenet and 10 [ICON_GOLD] Gold when you gift a Military Unit to a [ICON_CITY_STATE] City-State, scaling with Era.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- BIMARISTAN -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_BIMARISTAN">
			<Text>Bimaristan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_BIMARISTAN_TEXT">
			<Text>The Bimaristan were centers for medical treatment, the precursor to the modern Hospital. The Arab world was notable for several medical practices which have become commonplace today including separating patients by their ailments into wards, the development of patient medical records, the secularization of medical care, and standards for medical practitioners, including examinations and licensing. Bimaristans were paid for by charitable endowments called Waqfs. This guaranteed that the operations and cost of treatment would be borne by the institution, regardless of the patient's race, religion, gender, or social standing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_BIMARISTAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Arabian replacement for the University. In addition to the bonuses of a University, the Bimaristan generates additional yields when you purchase anything with Faith, and grants additional Food for each specialist worked.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARABIA_BIMARISTAN_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Jungle and Snow tiles worked by this City. Gain 25% of the [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output of the City as an instant boost to your current Research when a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in this City. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_RESEARCH] Illiteracy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gain 15% of the Cost of any [ICON_PEACE] Faith Purchase as [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_FOOD] Food in this City. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food to all Specialists.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Buffalo Pound -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 4/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND">
			<Text>Buffalo Pound</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 4 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for each Encampment constructed on land owned by this City.
			[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.
			[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.
			[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.
			[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Buffalo Pound is the Shoshone unique building, replacing both the Well and the Watermill. In addition to the benefits of those buildings, the Buffalo Pound can be built anywhere and provides additional yields from Horses, Cattle, Sheep and Bison. Each encampment on a tile owned by a city with a Buffalo Pound gives additional gold in the city, even if the Encampment is not being worked. With the Buffalo Pound, you can continue to benefit from encampments beyond the population or working radius of your cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOSHONE_BUFFALO_POUND_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Buffalo Pounds were large constructions built by many Plains Tribes for the entrapment and killing of Buffalo. Large herds of buffalo were corralled and funneled into the pound, a sturdy circular ring of hides and wood, where tribesmen could throw spears and other missile weapons from the safety of the walls.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Buffalo were a staple food source on the North American Plains, but hunting such large animals was difficult without horses or sturdy weapons. With the arrival of Europeans and the introduction of the horse and musket, Native American tribes could travel great distances and attack bison herds with impunity. The good times would not last, however, as Europeans encroached upon this way of life. Increasingly, the Great Plains were converted into farms and pastures for American homesteaders. The American buffalo was driven to the brink of extinction by a combination of habitat loss, industrial-scale hunting, and culls engineered to starve the indigenous population.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Today, American buffalo have recovered, but their range has been greatly limited to a few national parks. Commercial farming and sport hunting continues, but the buffalo are unlikely to ever return to their historical numbers.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Bullring -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan 12/10/2020 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SPAIN_BULLRING">
			<Text>Bullring</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SPAIN_BULLRING_HELP">
			<Text>+500 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science when completed. Nearby Jungle, Forest, and Pastures gain +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. When any [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Route originating here and targeting another Civ is completed, receive a [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism boost with the Civ based on your recent [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Trigger a "We Love the King Day" in this city whenever it completes a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Public Works Project[ENDCOLOR]. Gain 100 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_PEACE] Faith, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold whenever a "We Love the King Day" begins, Scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]-1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_CULTURE] Boredom.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SPAIN_BULLRING_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Bullring is a Spanish unique building that is cheaper and is available earlier than the Zoo. In addition to the Zoo's bonuses to Forest and Jungle, the Bullring gives bonuses to Pastures. Try to focus on triggering many "We Love the King Days" by connecting resources or building Public Works in order to get additional yields.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SPAIN_BULLRING_TEXT">
			<Text>An exceptionally old and irrepressible institution, Spanish bullfighting can trace its roots back to pre-Roman pagan bull cults. The modern incarnation of Spanish bullfighting traces its roots to the ceremonial and stylistic innovations of virtuoso bullfighters and the construction of the first dedicated Bullrings in the late 1700s. From there, Spain's bullfighting traditions have spread to all of her former colonies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Cacadores -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES">
			<Text>Cacador</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Cacadores were the elite light infantry of the Portuguese army in the 18th and 19th centuries. The divisions were famed for their marksmanship and their brown coats, one of the first attempts at military camouflage. After Portugal's sound defeat and occupation by Napoleon, the English intervened on behalf of their ally to rally and reorganize a joint war to retake the country. The British general, William Beresford, formed the Cacadores to fill a skirmishing role analogous to the German jaegers or American ranger divisions. Under this combined military, the Cacadores helped in reclaiming Portuguese independence and distinguished themselves as the "fighting cocks" of the Portuguese army until the units were eventually dissolved in the military reforms of 1911.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Cacador is the unique Portuguese replacement for the Gatling Gun. It gains recon promotions by leveling up, allowing it to excel in hostile terrain.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PORTUGUESE_CACADORES_HELP">
			<Text>
				Ranged unit of the Industrial era. Only Portugal may build it. Whenever it levels up, it gains a random Promotion from the Trailblazer or Survivalism lines. Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Covering Fire I[ENDCOLOR].
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PORTUGAL_CACADOR">
			<Text>Fighting Cock</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PORTUGAL_CACADOR_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gets a free Trailblazer or Survivalism promotion [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Levelling[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Chaebol -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOREA_CHAEBOL">
			<Text>Chaebol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOREA_CHAEBOL_HELP">
			<Text>City must have a Bank. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for Towns and Villages near the City. Cost of [ICON_GOLD] Gold purchasing in this City reduced by 25%.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+4 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for Factories in this City. All Chaebols gain +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for every Chaebol on Empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOREA_CHAEBOL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Chaebol is the unique Stock Exchange replacement for South Korea. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Stock Exchange, the Chaebol boosts the production of Factories in Cities where the Chaebol is built and boost every other Chaebol in the empire. The more Chaebols you build, the more they produce, allowing Korea to pursue a powerful economic advantage with enough cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOREA_CHAEBOL_PEDIA">
			<Text>
				Chaebol are powerful multi-national corporations originating in South Korea. Beginning as family businesses, generous government investment allowed the Chaebols to quickly industrialize South Korea's agricultural society, in what was called the Miracle on the Han River. The Chaebol became central to the South Korean economy and came to represent the invincibility of South Korea’s industrial might until the financial crashes the late 20th century, which saw several important Chaebol declare bankruptcy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Chaebol continue to dominate the South Korean economy and social fabric, and some like Samsung and Hyundai have become household names worldwide. Today, Chaebol account for over 80% of South Korea's exports, and the largest single Chaebol accounts for 17% of the entire nation's GDP.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Charbagh -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 16/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_PERSIA_CHARBAGH">
			<Text>Charbagh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_PERSIA_CHARBAGH_TEXT">
			<Text>A Charbagh is a walled garden divided into four square sections that is distinctive to Indo-Persian culture. These gardens trace their roots to the pairidaeza of the Achaemenid empire, and perhaps back even further to Assyrian garden designs. Charbagh construction was an invaluable a tool of state, demonstrating a king’s ability to bring life to an otherwise desolate area; the angular, ordered construction served as a contrast the chaos of nature. Persian and later Persianized cultures employed garden building as a subtle way to demonstrate the King of King's command over his realm and the natural world within it through the creation of public spaces.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Persian gardens have captured the imaginations of Mediterranean and western thinkers. The pairidaeza is the root of the Greek “paradise”, informing modern notions of an earthly Eden in art and poetry.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Charbagh can be built by [ICON_WORKER] Workers on Land with access to Fresh Water, and not next to another Charbagh.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Charbagh yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. During a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age, the Charbagh's yields are increased by +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, in addition to the usual +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+5% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People Points in City for each worked Charbagh.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_PERSIA_CHARBAGH_HELP">
			<Text>The Charbagh can be built by [ICON_WORKER] Workers on Land with access to Fresh Water, and not next to another Charbagh.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Charbagh yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. During a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age, the Charbagh's yields are increased by +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, in addition to the usual +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+5% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People Points in City for each worked Charbagh.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_PERSIA_CHARBAGH">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_PERSIA_CHARBAGH]Charbagh[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_PERSIA_CHARBAGH_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Charbagh, which increases [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and increases the rate of [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People generation.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_PERSIA_CHARBAGH_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People generation rate.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Chasqui -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUI">
			<Text>Chasqui</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUI_HELP">
			<Text>Flexible Scout and Support Unit of the Classical Era. Only the Inca may build it. Gains +1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Moves and Heals faster in Friendly Territory. Moves at Double Speed in [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Mountains[ENDCOLOR]. Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Medic I[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Chasqui is the unique Scout replacement for the Inca. This unit moves quickly through Mountains and friendly territory. The Chasqui also starts with medic I, making it a flexible and accessible early support unit for your main fighting force.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUI_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Chasquis were the messengers of the Inca Empire in charge of carrying messages and gifts up to 240 km per day through a form of on-foot Pony Express. In addition to their physical fitness, Chasquis were well-educated, able to translate the khipus, the Incan knot-based writing system, to each other and higher authorities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Chasquis were dispatched along thousands of miles of Andean trails, taking advantage of a vast system of roads and rope bridges maintained throughout the mountains of Peru and Ecuador. Tambos, or relay stations, were used for the chasquis to stop at and transfer messages to the next chasqui. Each Chasqui carried a conch trumpet which was blown to signal to a fresh chasqui that one runner was close so that they could prepare to run.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUIWASI">
			<Text>Chasquiwasi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INCA_CHASQUIWASI_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Heal 5 Additional HP[ENDCOLOR] per turn when in [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Friendly Territory[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]Double Movement in [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Mountains[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Corsair -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCO_CORSAIR">
			<Text>Corsair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCO_CORSAIR_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Barbary Corsairs were Muslim pirates and privateers operating off the coast of North Africa who became infamous throughout Europe. Ranging throughout the Mediterranean and as far as Iceland, the Corsairs slaughtered livestock and captured Christians for sale in the slave markets of the Islamic world. The frequency and ferocity of these raids, or "Razzia" was such that long stretches of Italian and Spanish coast were abandoned for fear of abduction. It is estimated that some 1.25 million people were enslaved by Barbary corsairs between 1530 and 1780 A.D.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The scope of Corsair activity began to diminish in the latter part of the 17th century, as the more powerful European navies started to pose a real threat to the Barbary States. However, Christian shipping and coastlines continued to suffer until the early 19th century. Following the Napoleonic Wars and the Congress of Vienna in 1814, European powers agreed upon the need to suppress the Barbary Corsairs for good. The razzias finally ceased after the Second Barbary War between the Barbary pirates and the United States, the impetus for the creation of the US Navy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"It is written in our Koran, that all nations which do not acknowledge the Prophet are sinners, whom it is the right and duty of the faithful to plunder and enslave; and that every mu'min (believer) who is slain in this warfare is sure to go to paradise."[NEWLINE]
				-Sidi Haji Abdrahaman, to Thomas Jefferson in reply to his demand for the protection of American merchant ships
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCO_CORSAIR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Corsair is the unique Moroccan replacement for the Corvette. It specializes in raiding and pillaging maritime trade routes, earning Food and Production for each enemy unit killed and trade route plundered. The unit can enter other Civilization's borders, even without an open borders agreement, which can be exploited to disrupt better protected trade routes.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MOROCCO_CORSAIR_HELP">
			<Text>Naval Unit specializing in disrupting maritime trade. Only Morocco may build it. Can enter Rival Territory. Gain [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production whenever a Corsair Kills a Units, Pillages a Resource, or Plunders a [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Route.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MOROCCO_RAZZIA">
			<Text>Razzia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MOROCCO_RAZZIA_HELP">
			<Text>Gain [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in your [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill, Pillage or Trade Route Plunder[ENDCOLOR]. Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can Enter Enemy Territory[ENDCOLOR] without Open Borders Agreement.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dhanurgraha -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 4/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_EPIC">
			<Text>Epic</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_EPIC_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and additional XP [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR]. [ICON_CULTURE] Culture doubled [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Barbarian Kills[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURVIDYA">
			<Text>Dhanurvidya</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURVIDYA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_PEACE] Faith [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Promotion[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI">
			<Text>Dhanurdhara</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI_HELP">
			<Text>Potent early Archery Unit. Only India may build it. Slightly stronger than Archer which it replaces. Gains [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and bonus XP for every kill, and gains [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when levelling up. [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from kills is doubled against Barbarians.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Dhanurdhara is a powerful defense against early barbarians which helps India maintain its cultural and religious dominance in the early game. Seek out barbarians to kill for culture and faith, then turn on your neighbours if it suits you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDIA_DHANURAASHI_TEXT">
			<Text>Archery was the most highly revered martial art of ancient India. Many of the culture heroes and gods of the Vedic texts describe archers of unparalleled skill, including Arjuna, Rama, Karna, and even Shiva himself. Traditional Indian bows are described as long, matching the height of their users, but without the tremendous strength of the Welsh longbow.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Djong -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDONESIA_CETBANG">
			<Text>Cetbang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INDONESIA_CETBANG_HELP">
			<Text>10 Damage to all adjacent enemy Units [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]each Turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_DJONG">
			<Text>Djong</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_DJONG_TEXT">
			<Text>At the time of their creation in the 1st century CE, the Djong were easily the largest, most capable seagoing vessels anywhere in the world. Averaging at over 400 tons of cargo and capable of withstanding the typhoon winds, these marvels of engineering extended the Javanese trade networks from northern China to Ghana. At the time of the Majapahit Empire, Djong were armed with the earliest breech-loading cannons, the brass cetbang, which helping them conquer the entire Indonsesian Archipelago. Djong were still widely used until the 16th century, and the methods for designing Djong ships spread throughout Asia, influencing the creation of China's iconic junk boats.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_DJONG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Djong is a replacement for the Galleass, but behaves like an early Frigate, able to move normally in deep ocean and fire from 2 tiles away. Use Djong in combination with melee units to create a seaworthy navy before any other civilization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDONESIA_DJONG_HELP">
			<Text>Massive ranged naval unit. Only Indonesia may build it. Moves at full speed in deep ocean and attack from a distance. Damages all nearby enemy units each turn.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Doelen -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius on 17/11/2017, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo 13/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_SCHUTTERIJ">
			<Text>Doelen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_SCHUTTERIJ_HELP">
			<Text>+25 [ICON_SPY] City Security, plus 1 for every two [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. When you capture or identify a foreign Spy in this City, gain 50 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science in this City for every Global Monopoly on Empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contains 1 slot for a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Art or Artifact. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_FOOD] and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Distress.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_SCHUTTERIJ_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Doelen is the Netherlands' unique replacement for the Constabulary. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Constabulary, the Doelen provides bonuses to Defense and rewards you for capturing and identifying enemy spies in your cities. The Doelen gets stronger with the total number of global monopolies, both luxury and strategic that the Dutch control. Trade vigorously to leverage your Doelen's potential strengths.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NETHERLANDS_SCHUTTERIJ_TEXT">
			<Text>Within the cities of the Low Countries, the institution of policing has its roots in the schutterij, a voluntary town watch and citizen militia. Membership in the town's schuttersgilde was often undertaken by wealthy burghers as a stepping stone for further public posts in the city. The Schutterij were responsible for military support during a siege or revolt, fire, and for closing and re-opening the city gates each day. Because of their secondary function as social clubs for wealthy and ambitious young men, the schutterij held undue influence over municipal politics, and often took upon themselves additional responsibilities such as hosting public banquets, religious functions, and philanthropic work. The officers regularly paid for group portraits of the members, some of which are still highly regarded as the finest paintings produced by the Dutch Golden Age[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			The training grounds for schutters were called Doelen, meaning "target range". Doelen typically were placed near the city walls and consisted of an outdoor firing range with an adjoining hall for gymnastic exercise and meetings. Many Doelen throughout the Netherlands have been preserved, though often converted into school gymnasiums, libraries, or community halls.</Text>
		</Row>

	
		<!-- Dromon -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_0">
			<Text>Greek Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_0_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]After Attack[ENDCOLOR] Defending Enemy Unit is marked, reducing its Max HP by [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]20[ENDCOLOR] and Healing by [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]10[ENDCOLOR] for [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]2[ENDCOLOR] turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_1">
			<Text>Raging Fire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_GREEK_FIRE_1_HELP">
			<Text>-20 Maximum HP and -10 HP [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]on Heal[ENDCOLOR]. Both effects last [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]2[ENDCOLOR] turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON">
			<Text>Dromon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON_HELP">
			<Text>A powerful Naval Ranged Unit. Only the Byzantines may build it. Attacks by a Dromon reduce the target's Max HP by 20 and their Healing by 10 for 2 turns. Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Splash Damage I I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Bring flaming death to your enemies. Stronger than the Liburna it replaces, and deals additional burning damage to both the target unit and any enemies near the Dromon. It cannot end its turn in Deep Ocean tiles outside of the city borders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BYZANTIUM_DROMON_TEXT">
			<Text>A modified form of the traditional galley, the Dromon was an integral part of the Byzantine navy throughout the empire's reign. Featuring both oar and sail power, the Dromon was highly maneuverable and agile, but also dangerously equipped for battle. Through the use of Greek Fire, a precursor to modern Napalm, the Byzantines struck fear into the hearts of any who opposed them on the sea.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Dummies -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 29/08/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_BARBICAN">
			<Text>DF Barbican</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>DF Oppidum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_PROXENOS">
			<Text>DF Proxenos</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_HUEY">
			<Text>DF Huey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_GUMEY">
			<Text>DF Gumey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_BUFFALO">
			<Text>DF Buffalo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_FLAX">
			<Text>DF Flax</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_GUMEY_LUX">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for all Nearby Luxuries</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_1">
			<Text>DF Sachem 1</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_2">
			<Text>DF Sachem 2</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_3">
			<Text>DF Sachem 3</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_4">
			<Text>DF Sachem 4</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_5">
			<Text>DF Sachem 5</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_6">
			<Text>DF Sachem 6</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SACHEM_7">
			<Text>DF Sachem 7</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_QILA_1">
			<Text>DF Qila 1</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_QILA_2">
			<Text>DF Qila 2</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_TEUTONIC">
			<Text>DF Teutonic</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_D_FOR_BARBICAN">
			<Text>Fortifications</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_TERSANE">
			<Text>DF Tersane</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_D_FOR_GUMEY">
			<Text>Suguba</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SCHUTTERIJ">
			<Text>DF Doelen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_RIAD">
			<Text>DF Riad</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_SALON">
			<Text>DF Salon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_CHAEBOL">
			<Text>DF Chaebol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_HIPPODROME">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_GOLD] Gold [ICON_CULTURE] Culture during [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] WLTKD</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_BAAN">
			<Text>DF Baan Chang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_TELPOCHCALLI">
			<Text>DF Telpochcalli</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_LATIFUNDIUM">
			<Text>DF Villa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_FORNIX">
			<Text>Eliminated Civilizations and City-States</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_POGOST">
			<Text>DF Pogost</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_ALTICUR">
			<Text>DF Alti Cur</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_CHARBAGH">
			<Text>DF Charbagh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_IDEOLOGY">
			<Text>Dummy Ideology Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_PANTHEON">
			<Text>Dummy Pantheon Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_FOUNDER">
			<Text>Dummy Founder Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_ENHANCER">
			<Text>Dummy Enhancer Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_REFORMATION">
			<Text>Dummy Reformation Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_BYZANTIUM">
			<Text>Dummy BYZANTIUM Building</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOPHET_DUMMY">
			<Text>DF Shofet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_QULLQA">
			<Text>1 [ICON_RES_COCA] Coca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_BEER_HALL_FREEDOM">
			<Text>DF Brauhaus Freedom</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_BEER_HALL_ORDER">
			<Text>DF Brauhaus Order</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_D_FOR_BEER_HALL_AUTOCRACY">
			<Text>DF Brauhaus Autocracy</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- E-temenanki -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 28/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI">
			<Text>E-temenanki</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] GPP in the City. +25 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City as an instant boost whenever a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born and +50 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points whenever a Policy is unlocked, scaling with Era. Gain 15% of the City's [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output whenever you invest in a Building on Empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to all Monuments and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food to all Shrines.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires Monument in City. Can only be built in the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital. The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>E-temenanki is the Babylonian Unique Wonder, replacing the National Monument. In addition to the normal bonuses of a National Monument, E-temenanki awards Food and Science whenever a building is invested on empire, so invest in buildings early and often.  All monuments in empire gain +1 Science and all Shrines gain +2 Food.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BABYLON_ETEMENANKI_TEXT">
			<Text>E-temenanki was the Ziggurat of Marduk, god of storms and head of the Babylonian pantheon. Ziggurats were religious temples erected in Mesopotamian cities as the literal homes for the city's patron god. It was believed that the gods originally lived in the high mountains, so Ziggurats took the form of artificial mountains inside the city to make their resident god feel more comfortable.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Examination Hall -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHINA_EXAMINATION_HALL">
			<Text>Examination Hall</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHINA_EXAMINATION_HALL_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Perhaps the greatest legacy of Chinese culture is the Imperial Examination system with which the Son of Heaven's empire was staffed with civil servants for over two millennia. The Imperial examinations represented an attempt to create an aristocracy of learning, a remarkable advance over the warrior and hereditary aristocracies that dominated the rest of the world. Amounting to tests of rote memorization, the examinations required direct quotations of Confucian philosophy and ethics from the Five Confucian Classics. A scholar who obtained the highest degree, the jinshi, would have his memory trained to a tremendous degree.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				As Western universities began to move away from their own classical tradition to embrace economics, engineering and natural science, China's scholarly efforts languished in the ancient literary past. Under pressure to modernize, the examinations were abolished in 1890 by Dowager Empress Cixi, leaving behind a legacy as the first system of intellectual meritocracy the world had ever seen.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				“We tried an experiment which is unique in the history of the world: We sought to rule this great country not by force, but by wisdom. And for centuries we succeeded.”[NEWLINE]
				-Anonymous Confucian Philosopher; excerpt from "On a Chinese Screen"
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHINA_EXAMINATION_HALL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Examination Hall is a Chinese unique building, replacing the Chancery. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Chancery, the Exam Hall boosts Great People generation in the city, adding Great Person Points to whichever great person currently has the most points in the city whenever a citizen is born.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHINA_EXAMINATION_HALL_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of Diplomatic Units. Grants the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Royal Signet[ENDCOLOR] Promotion to all Diplomatic Units built in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every Ally.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Whenever a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born, gain +15 [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] points toward [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person with the highest progress, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works in this City</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Figs -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 25/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_ROME_FIGS">
			<Text>Figs</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_ROME_FIGS_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_ROME_FIGS_TEXT">
			<Text>Native to the Middle East and western Asia, Figs have been cultivated since ancient times, being one of the oldest plants cultivated by humans. Figs were common in Ancient Greece and spread to Rome where they formed a staple fruit for the lower classes. Figs are easy to preserve and are well-suited to forming condiments due to their high sugar content. It is perhaps this very association with the simplicity and poverty of common folk which saw figs fall from fashion in later periods.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Fornix -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan on 30/05/2024 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TECH_TRIUMPH_TITLE">
			<Text>Fornix</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TECH_TRIUMPH_DESC">
			<Text>You have delved too greedily and too deep.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TECH_TRIUMPH_HELP">
			<Text>Secret</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_TRIUMPH">
			<Text>Triumph</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_TRIUMPH_TEXT">
			<Text>A Triumph is granted when an enemy Civilization or City-State is defeated. A Triumph allows you to construct a new Fornix in any city within your empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROME_FORNIX">
			<Text>Fornix</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROME_FORNIX_HELP">
			<Text>Receive 1 [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GREAT_WRITER] Great Writer and starts 10 turns of "We Love the King Day" in the City in which it is built. Aqueducts in this City gain an additional +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism, and all other Aqueducts on Empire gain +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Land Units created by this City (past or future) receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Morale[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, which gives +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength. [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Military Units Supplied by this City''s population increased by 10%. Contains 1 slot for a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Writing.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROME_FORNIX} can be constructed without limitation. 1 additional {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROME_FORNIX} can be built for each Civilization or [ICON_CITY_STATE] City-State you have [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]eliminated[ENDCOLOR]. The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROME_FORNIX_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Fornix is the Roman unique wonder, replacing the Heroic Epic. Unlike other national wonders, the Fornix can be built more than once in your empire. The first Fornix can be built without restriction in any city, but you can build additional Fornices for each Civilization or City-State you eliminate. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Heroic Epic, the Fornix triggers a "We Love The King Day" in the city when constructed, and boosts all Arenas in your empire. Take advantage of your considerable bonuses for conquering City-States to build multiple Fornices in your empire, stacking their global yields, and multiple free Great Writers.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROME_FORNIX_TEXT">
			<Text>A Roman Triumphal Arch, or Fornix, are freestanding archways designed to span over roadways, a monument you can walk through that is emblematic of Roman architecture. During the Roman Republic, Fornices were constructed in honour of generals who led the Romans to a great victory. The general would lead a parade through the city of Rome until arriving at the senate. Often the festivities were prolonged by a series of games and banquets. Late imperial Romans emulated the semi-mythical tradition of the triumph and its arches, but the archways started to be used more loosely to commemorate the deaths of various emperors, the founding of new colonies, and the construction of other infrastructure. The use of large arches as war memorials has continued to the present day.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Fusta -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VENICE_FUSTA">
			<Text>Fusta</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VENICE_FUSTA_HELP">
			<Text>A small and fast compliment to the Great Galleas, rather than a replacement. Weaker, but cheaper, and does not cost Unit [ICON_GOLD] Gold Maintenance or [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Military Supply.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VENICE_FUSTA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Fusta are quick, cheap, and do not cost any unit maintenance. Use these ships in combination with the bigger Galleass to monitor and protect your shipping lanes without causing an undue burden on your economy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VENICE_FUSTA_TEXT">
			<Text>Fusta, or galliots, were small galleys with no more than 35 sailors. Exceptionally light and fast, the Venetians originally used them to maintain a standing navy against pirates, but the ship quickly became a favorite of the pirates themselves. The shallow draft, maneuverability and speed of the Fusta made them a legend throughout the Mediterranean.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Holkan -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 16/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_SCOUT_GOODY_BONUS_2">
			<Text>Lost Codices</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_SCOUT_GOODY_BONUS_2_HELP">
			<Text>+25% Yields, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Ancient Ruins[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN">
			<Text>Holkan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN_HELP">
			<Text>A dangerous scout with no penalty against Barbarians. Only the Maya may build it. Gains [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture with every Ancient Ruin explored. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Trailblazer I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Holkan is a quick and independent scout for the Maya. Because of their free Trailblazer I promotion, the Holkan explores more quickly, and gains experience more easily than the Pathfinders. Their increased power against barbarians makes Holkans capable of ranging farther and taking more risks than a normal scout. Use these units to grab ruins quickly, and gain an early scientific edge and cultural edge.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAYA_HOLKAN_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Maya are often idealized as a peaceful civilization by western historians, but the Maya were not strangers to war. Unlike the wars of Europe and Asia, however, the Maya engaged in a highly ritualized form of combat based on astrological and religious concerns as much as political ones. Squabbles over land, influence, and resources were common, but the need for human sacrifices was also a factor leading to war.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The nobility and priesthood of Mayan cities kept a monopoly on violence, making all but the most desperate of wars strictly within the affairs of the upper class. Weapons made of obsidian and chert were stockpiled within the palaces of lords and kings, who would call upon their family to lead raids. The leaders of such expeditions were known as ‘Holkan’.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Great Turkish Bombard -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 1/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SIEGE_INACCURACY_2">
			<Text>Siege Inaccuracy II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SIEGE_INACCURACY_2_HELP">
			<Text>-50% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Land Units[ENDCOLOR]. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SAHI_TOPU">
			<Text>Sahi Topu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_OTTOMANS_SAHI_TOPU_HELP">
			<Text>Unit deals 15 damage to itself [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Attack[ENDCOLOR]. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_1">
			<Text>Basilica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_2">
			<Text>Dardanelles Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_3">
			<Text>Mohammed's Great Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_4">
			<Text>Orban's Cannon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_5">
			<Text>Kalle Acici</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD">
			<Text>Great Bombard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_HELP">
			<Text>An Incredibly powerful Unit capable of smashing Cities to pieces. Only the Ottomans may build it. Does very high damage to Cities and Naval Units, but is less useful against Land Units compared to other Siege Weapons.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Deals 15 damage to itself on attack.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Player may have only [COLOR_GREEN]2[ENDCOLOR] Great Bombards at one time.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Great Bombard is a powerful Siege Weapon well after it is researched. It is the most powerful seige unit in its era; so dangerous it even hurts itself! Devastating against cities and naval units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTTOMANS_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Bigger is better, and biggest is best. The super-sized bombards of the late medieval were first used in Western European warfare at the beginning of the 15th century, but it was the Ottomans that would realize the bombard's full potential at the Siege of Constantinople in 1453. Unable to find patronage with the Byzantine emperor, a Hungarian gunfounder named Orban sold his services to Mehmed II of the Ottoman Empire, and began crafting bronze cannons capable of lobbing 1.6 tons of shaped stone more than a mile.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Transporting such massive weapons took as many as 60 oxen, and required construction of entire road networks before the cannons could be brought to bear against the impregnable Theodosian Walls. Within a day of the opening bombardment, massive stones smashed the outer defenses to rubble and the city which had stood as a fortress of Christendom for a millennium fell. The sack of Constantinople raged for three days following, and triggered a mass exodus of Greeks into Europe proper. The influx of Byzantine refugees brought a rediscovery of the philosophical and intellectual achievements of Greek culture into Western Europe, planting the seeds of the Renaissance.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Stone bombards were supplanted by iron-ball cannons by the end of the 16th century, and few bombards are left intact. None of the bombard’s descendants, however, can claim to have single-handedly ended an era.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Goedendag -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius on 28/10/2017, modified and incorporated by adan_eslavo on 12/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG">
			<Text>Goedendag</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_HELP">
			<Text>A cheap, versatile Defensive unit with supporting abilities. Only the Dutch may build it. Provides a combat boost to all Units adjacent to it and has increased [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if Garrisoned in a City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Goedendag is an odd unit, but effective in groups. While effective on their own against cavalry, the Goedendag provides increased attack against all units adjacent to it, and has additional combat strength if Garrisoned in a City at the beginning of your turn. Goedendag's do not boost their own combat strength, so Goedendags must be adjacent to each other to receive the benefit of their own promotion. These units can be built very quickly, so an army can be raised in the event of a surprise war.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A Goedendag is a four-foot long club with a spearhead at its tip that was used by the militias of Medieval Flanders during the Franco-Flemish War. The weapon was christened "goedendag" by the French, a cognate with the Dutch greeting "good day". This name may be a reference to the Bruges Matins massacre of 1302, in which the guildsmen of Bruges took over the city by greeting people in the streets and murdering anyone who answered with a French accent.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Goedendags were used to great effect by the guildsmen of Flanders against the French knights, but exactly how the weapon was used is a source of debate. Contemporary illustrations show it being used as a club, written accounts describe its first use as a spear to meet a charge, then a club as the enemy was halted. However they worked, men armed with Goedendags marked the beginning of the end for heavy cavalry in Western Europe, and the dawn of an "Infantry Revolution" where peasant militia were now a credible threat to professional soldiers. The stunning victory of common men over foreign tyrants became a wellspring of romantic nationalism for the Low Countries.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"each held his godendart (sic) raised against the French, the iron as one meets a wild boar"[NEWLINE]- Guillaume Guiart, a contemporary account describing the battle of Courtrai, 1302 A.D.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG">
			<Text>Goedendag!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_GOEDENDAG_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to adjacent Friendly Land Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_BURGEMEESTE">
			<Text>Burgemeeste</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_NETHERLANDS_BURGEMEESTE_HELP">
			<Text>+33% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]within 2 tiles of a Friendly City[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Gumey -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan on 29/08/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SONGHAI_GUMEY">
			<Text>Gumey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SONGHAI_GUMEY_HELP">
			<Text>When a [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Land Trade Route originating here and targeting another Civ is completed, receive a [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism boost with the Civ based on recent [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 2 Desert or Tundra tiles worked by the City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Land Trade Routes gain +75% Range and +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Incoming [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes generate +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for the City and the Trade Route Owner. +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture if a [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Unit passes through the City.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_TRUFFLES] Truffles: +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COTTON] Cotton: +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_FUR] Furs: +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to all Nearby Luxuries.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SONGHAI_GUMEY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Gumey is a Songhai unique building that replaces the Caravansary. The Gumey provides much larger bonuses to trade than the normal Caravansary, boosting International Trade Routes, and extra yields if a trade route passes through the city. Expand your empire's territory and reap the economic benefits of a vast trade empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SONGHAI_GUMEY_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Gumeys were riverside entrepots used to conduct goods and soldiers back and forth along the Niger river before they were loaded onto camels for the arduous journey across the open desert. Even before gaining their independence from the Mali Empire, the Songhai had become fantastically wealthy off the trade of gold, salt, and slaves from the Trans-Saharan trade routes. The Songhai's seat of power lay at the edge of the vast Saharan desert, acting as a waystation between the Taghazan salt mines to the north, the gold mines in the southwest, and distant markets in Egypt and the Middle East. 
			</Text>
		</Row>	

		<!-- Gymnasium -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_GYMNASIUM">
			<Text>Gymnasion</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_GREECE_GYMNASIUM_TEXT">
			<Text>The Gymnasion were training facilities used by adult Greek men to socialize and practice for public games. The name roughly translates to "naked training place", because all athletes practiced while naked, and usually while covered in olive oil. Gymnasia started as open fields outside city limits, but were later planned as enclosed spaces that were central to Greek public life. While the public games and festivals were important themselves, Gymnasia also became centers of arts and learning. The famous schools of philosophy in Athens -- the Academic school founded by Plato, the Peripatetic School founded by Aristotle, and the Cynic school founded by Antisthenes -- were all founded and named after the Gymnasia where they met.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_GYMNASIUM_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Greek replacement for the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMPHITHEATER}. In addition to the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMPHITHEATER}'s bonuses, {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREECE_GYMNASIUM} produces [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_CULTURE_LOCAL] Border Growth Points when your unit defeats an enemy unit.</Text>
		</Row>	

		<!-- Hashemite Raider -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER">
			<Text>Hashemite Raider</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Long considered the "Sick Man of Europe", Ottoman power was in decline well before nationalist sentiment took root in the Arab population. When WWI broke out among the European powers the Ottomans set about crushing Arab dissent. Arab citizens responded in a popular revolt, declaring a new Islamic empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Hussein bin Ali, Sharif of Mecca, began the rebellion in hopes of re-establishing a Hashemite dynasty in Arabia, and led his fellow Arabs in armed rebellion against their Turkish masters in Hejaz. Seeing an opportunity to tie down Ottoman forces in a new front, the British promised to recognize Arab hegemony and heavily subsidize the revolt, sending the now famous T.E. Lawrence as a liaison. With this new infusion of funds and equipment, the Arabs waged a guerilla war through the desert, crippling Ottoman supply lines. With the help of French and English navy, they were able to take several ports along the Mediterranean coast, emboldening even more to join their cause.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				With the end of WWI in 1918 and the Ottomans’ defeat, the Arabs expected the full cooperation of their European allies as they established their new kingdom. However, the English and French had other plans. Behind closed doors, the French and English secretly formed the Sykes-Picot Agreement which divided the Middle-East amongst their own respective spheres of influence. This gross betrayal of a trusted ally has soured relations between the Arab states and the West ever since.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Hashemite Raider the Arab replacement for the Light Tank. It is adept at hit-and-run tactics and disrupting enemy supply lines. Whenever it pillages an improvement, adjacent enemy units take 10 damage. Moves quickly through desert.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARABIA_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_HELP">
			<Text>Fast and dangerous Modern Era Cavalry Unit. Only Arabia may build it. Available earlier, and does not require [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum. Moves faster and is stronger in Desert. Does not require [ICON_MOVES] Movement to pillage Tile Improvements, and deals damage to adjacent Enemy Units whenever it Pillages a tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ARABIA_GARLAND_MINE">
			<Text>Garland Mine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ARABIA_GARLAND_MINE_HELP">
			<Text>Unit uses [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]no[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement Points [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR]. All [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]adjacent Enemy Units[ENDCOLOR] take 15 damage [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ARABIA_DESERT_RAIDER">
			<Text>Desert Raider</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ARABIA_DESERT_RAIDER_HELP">
			<Text>Double [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement and +25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Desert[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Hippodrome -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 2/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME">
			<Text>Hippodrome</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME_HELP">
			<Text>Does not require an Arena in the City. [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] Arena in the City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides 2 [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses. +15% [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on Empire during [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] 'We Love the King' Days.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]On construction of the Hippodrome, and at the beginning of every new Era, a [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] 'We Love the King' Day is triggered in all Cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Arenas gain +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and all Circuses gain +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on all sources of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses on Empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Hippodrome is the Byzantine Unique Wonder, replacing the Circus Maximus. In comparison to the Circus Maximus, The Hippodrome greatly increases Gold and Culture yields during "We Love the King Days" and begins a "We Love the King Day" on completion. All Arenas in the empire receive gold, while circuses receive Culture, and Horses get both.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Be careful to time when your transition into a new era comes, timing your free "We Love the King Day", to reset luxuries demanded in all cities.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BYZANTIUM_HIPPODROME_TEXT">
			<Text>Hippodromes were chariot racing tracks and the beating heart of Byzantine social and political life. Though slightly smaller in footprint than the Circus Maximus in Rome, there was no equal to the Hippodrome of Constantinople's grandeur, adorned with art and treasures from all corners of the empire. The Constantinople Hippodrome was built by Constantine himself shortly after he moved his capital to the city. The track was placed adjacent to the palace, taking the shape of a massive 'U', with ten monuments lining its center.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			Not just a pastime of the rich, the chariot races became the one place where the common people could see and interact with the emperor in a single venue. Commoners took the opportunity to begin chants for political or religious reforms during sporting events. Four political parties, or demes, existed within Constantinople which each sponsored a different racing team: The Blues, the Whites, the Greens and the Reds. Enormous sums of money were wagered on the outcomes of these races, which became further heated by the religious, societal, and political leanings which each team came to represent. One such feud in particular would come to overshadow them all: the Nika riots.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] 
			During the reign of Justinian I (an ardent supporter of the Blues), a dispute arose concerning the conviction of two hooligans, arrested for murder from a prior riot. The sentencing of these men unified the Blues and the Greens against Justinian in a terrible mob, and disgruntled nobles seized the opportunity to try to depose him as revenge for Justinian’s new taxes. Though at first he considered fleeing, Justinian rallied his loyal generals to corral the rioters into the Hippodrome, where they were butchered by royal guardsmen and Gothic mercenaries. By the time the Nika riots had ended, half of Constantinople had been burned down and 30,000 people were killed -- the deadliest riot in world history.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Huey Teocalli -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_HUEY_TEOCALLI">
			<Text>Huey Teocalli</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_HUEY_TEOCALLI_TEXT">
			<Text>In the Aztec Empire, a teocalli was a terraced pyramid surmounted by a roofed temple, and acted as the site of all the important religious rituals in the town. The greatest of these teocalli was located in the heart of Tenochtitlan, the Huey Teocalli (or, according to the Spanish, the Templo Mayor) dedicated to a pair of gods: Huitzilopochtli, the god of war, and Tlaloc, the god of agriculture (an indication of what was important in Aztec culture). Each god had a separate temple, reached by separate staircases.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_HUEY_TEOCALLI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Huey Teocalli is the unique Aztec replacement for the Grand Temple. It does not require a Temple. In addition to the regular bonuses of a Grand Temple, the Huey Teocalli gives a large bonus to religious pressure in the city, boosts the yields of lakes and Armories, and immediately triggers a Golden Age on completion . Upon entering a Golden Age, the city with the Huey Teocalli immediately grows. The Huey Teocalli also generates additional Faith and Gold from Kills by a flat amount, in addition to the yields that scale from combat strength from the Aztec's unique Ability. If concluding a war to trigger a Golden Age, make sure you pick a new target quickly so you can benefit from additional yields on kills.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_HUEY_TEOCALLI_HELP">
			<Text>Triggers a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age on Completion. Adds 1 new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen to the city whenever a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age begins. During  a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age, +10 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_GOLD] Gold when a Unit defeats an Enemy Unit in battle, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food to all Temples and Armories on Empire.  +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Lakes worked by this City. Boosts Pressure of [ICON_RELIGION] Religious Majority emanating from this City by 100%. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contains 1 slot for [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Music. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_PEACE] Religious Unrest in all cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- InDuna -->	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ZULU_IBUTHO">
			<Text>Ibutho</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ZULU_IBUTHO_HELP">
			<Text>Grants [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]30 XP[ENDCOLOR] to a stacked Friendly Unit when [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Expended[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA">
			<Text>InDuna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The InDuna is a Zulu unique unit. May construct a Citadel. +15% Combat bonus to all Land units within 2 tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]InDuna can be expended to construct a unique Isibaya Tile Improvement. Expending an InDuna gives 30XP to a unit that was stacked with it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_HELP">
			<Text>This Zulu Unique Great Person replaces the Great General. Aside from the ability to boost nearby troops and construct a unique replacement for the Citadel, Expending an InDuna gives bonus XP to a Stacked Unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_TEXT">
			<Text>An InDuna can widely be translated to any leader of men, in commerce, in politics, and in war. An InDuna guided each regiment, or 'ibutho', of young Zulu men and he in turn answered to senior izinDuna who controlled the corps. One or more of these elder chiefs might accompany a big force on an important mission, but there was no single "field marshal" in command of all Zulu forces. Regimental izinDuna, like the non-commissioned officers of today's army, were important for morale and discipline. This was demonstrated during the battle of Isandlwana, where the army led by Ntshingwayo kaMahole outmaneuvered and destroyed a British column. Ntshingwayo kaMahole and his fellow izinDuna snuck a Zulu force of 20 000 men behind the British, hiding them in a valley only 7 miles from the British camp. When discovered sitting in complete silence by scouts, the izinDuna spurred their men into action and closed the remaining distance with lightning speed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_1">
			<Text>Mzilikazi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_2">
			<Text>Mbopa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_3">
			<Text>Ntshingwayo kaMahole</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_4">
			<Text>Nathaniel Isaacs</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_5">
			<Text>Ndlela kaSompisi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_6">
			<Text>Umgobhozi Ovela Entabeni</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_7">
			<Text>Nongalaza KaNondela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_8">
			<Text>Dabulamanzi kaMpande</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_9">
			<Text>Dambuza Nzobo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_10">
			<Text>Nqoboka Mthiyane</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_11">
			<Text>Mabhodla Mbuyazi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_12">
			<Text>Menziwa Biyela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_13">
			<Text>Gala ka Nodade</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_14">
			<Text>Vumindaba kaNthati</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_15">
			<Text>Mavumengwana kaNdlela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_16">
			<Text>Zibhebhu kaMaphitha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZULU_INDABA_17">
			<Text>Manyosi</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Iron Chariot -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT">
			<Text>Iron Chariot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT_TEXT">
			<Text>Before horses were bred to be big enough to carry men on their backs, Assyrian chariots were used to smash into and disperse enemy formations. These sturdy chariots were both a platform for archers and javelineers and a weapon in their own right, forming the first shock tactics of history. Recognizing the great value of horses as tools of war, Assyrians conquered portions of Media specifically for their esteemed horse lineages.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Assyria's Iron Chariots act as shock troops to control the battlefield. They excel at breaking enemy ranks. The Iron Chariot gains a bonus when on Open Terrain, but moves more slowly in Rough Terrain. Iron and Horse resources in excess of the number of Iron Chariots you own increase the efficacy of your chariots.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_CHARIOT_HELP">
			<Text>Durable shock cavalry of the Ancient Era. Only Assyria may build it. Gains [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength while on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Open Terrain[ENDCOLOR], but costs additional movement to enter [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Rough Terrain[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Does not require [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses, but gains +1 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if Player has sufficient [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses for all Iron Chariots, and again for [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ASSYRIA_SHOCK_CAVALRY">
			<Text>Shock Cavalry</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ASSYRIA_SHOCK_CAVALRY_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength when on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Open Terrain[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_AND_HORSE">
			<Text>Hard and Fast</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ASSYRIA_IRON_AND_HORSE_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Power if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Player has more Horses or Iron than Iron Chariot Units[ENDCOLOR]. Bonuses can stack. Lost after unit upgrade.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Iziko -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO">
			<Text>Iziko</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO_TEXT">
			<Text>
				An Iziko is a simple hearth used as a gathering place for Zulu communities. The fireplace was revered as a source for food, warmth, dreams, and ancestral ties. It is from these gatherings that a sense of community and identity was formed, and young Zulus could perform and bond.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The fireplace is used metaphorically for the "cooking of songs" in isicathamiya stage performances, a modern offshoot of traditional Zulu music. Dreams were an essential part of communicating with ancestors and formed part of a deeply rooted Zulu religion. Some isicathamiya musicians claim some of their songs were created in the spiritual realm or given to them by their ancestors.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"A person is a person because of other people"[NEWLINE]-Zulu proverb
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO_HELP">
			<Text>+33% [ICON_GREAT_WRITER] Great Writer Rate in the City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Whenever a unit gains a level, receive [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City, scaling with Unit level.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_DYE] Dyes: +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SILK] Silk: +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_LAPIS] Lapis Lazuli: +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_BRAZILWOOD] Brazilwood: +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contains 2 slots for Great Works of Writing[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when Themed</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Iziko is the unique Zulu replacement for the Amphitheater. In addition to the bonuses of an Amphitheater, the Iziko provides Culture in the City whenever a military unit gains a level, with higher levels granting more culture. Make war an essential part of your empire's cultural development.</Text>
		</Row>	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_ZULU_IZIKO">
			<Text>Collection of {2_CivAdjective} Folktales</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZULU_IZIKO_THEMING_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure the Great Work Slots are all filled with Writings either from your own Civilization, or from Civilizations other than your own.</Text>
		</Row>	

		<!-- Kabuki & the Japanese Guilds-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_KABUKI">
			<Text>Kabuki Theater</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_KABUKI_TEXT">
			<Text>Kabuki is a classical Japanese dance-drama known for the stylization of its drama and for the elaborate make-up worn by some of its performers. The art form was created in 1603 when Izumo no Okuni, a miko of Izumo-taisha, began performing a new style of dance drama in the dry riverbeds of Kyoto. Despite many the upheaval of Japans modernization, Kabuki remains the most popular of the traditional styles of Japanese drama, and has helped renew interest in other forms of traditional Japanese art.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_KABUKI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Kabuki is the unique Japanese replacement for the Opera House. On construction, Any guilds in the city are replaced with unique Japanese guilds.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAPAN_KABUKI_HELP">
			<Text>+5% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City. Internal [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes to or from this City generate 50 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when completed, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works in the City produce +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism. +33% [ICON_GREAT_MUSICIAN] Great Musician Rate. All Guilds produce +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Great Musician[ENDCOLOR] is born, Gain [ICON_PEACE] Faith equal to your Empire's [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output per turn.[NEWLINE]When a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Great Artist[ENDCOLOR] is born, gain [ICON_RESEARCH] Science equal to 2% of the Artist's potential [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points from [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Starting a Golden Age[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]When a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Great Writer[ENDCOLOR] is born, Gain [ICON_GOLD] Gold equal to 5% of the Writer's potential [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Political Treatise[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
	
		<!-- Kampong -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan; incorporated by adan_eslavo on 24/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG">
			<Text>Kampong</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_TEXT">
			<Text>The term ‘Sama-Bajau’ refers to a single ethnic group scattered between the modern day Philippines, Indonesia, and Malaysia. The Sama people live a semi-sedentary life in stilt villages or “kampongs” in coastal shallows, while Bajau refers to nomadic groups living in house boats. The Sama-Bajau defy national and ethnic borders, travelling and fishing between islands on the open ocean. The Sama-Bajau were frequently employed as privateers and raiders by the Srivijayan kingdoms. Bajau-Laut possess unique abilities which allow them to see better underwater, and dive longer and deeper than any other group of humans.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In recent years, the Bajau-Laut have been forced into sedentary lifestyles by various governments, and face discrimination as pagans, outsiders and squatters. A combination of overfishing and modernization threatens the Bajau’s nomadic traditions, as they have been forcibly resettled on land. Still, a few communities of Bajau-Laut ride their lepa lepa across the blue water of Southeast Asia, only traveling to shore a few times each year.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Kampong can be built by [ICON_WORKER] Embarked Workers on Coastal and Lake Tiles, and not next to another Kampong.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Kampong yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_HELP">
			<Text>The Kampong can be built by [ICON_WORKER] Embarked Workers on Coastal and Lake Tiles, and not next to another Kampong.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Kampong yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_INDONESIA_KAMPONG">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG]Kampong[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Kampong, which increases [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_INDONESIA_KAMPONG_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Kibitum -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 27/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_0">
			<Text>Legacy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_0_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense against [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ranged[ENDCOLOR] attacks.[NEWLINE]Unit gets +8% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]every 2 levels gained[ENDCOLOR] until level [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]12[ENDCOLOR], and level [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]15[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_1">
			<Text>Legacy I</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_1_HELP">
			<Text>+8% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_2">
			<Text>Legacy II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_2_HELP">
			<Text>+16% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_3">
			<Text>Legacy III</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_3_HELP">
			<Text>+24% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_4">
			<Text>Legacy IV</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_4_HELP">
			<Text>+32% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_5">
			<Text>Legacy V</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_5_HELP">
			<Text>+40% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_6">
			<Text>Legacy VI</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_6_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_7">
			<Text>A Winner is You</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BABYLON_LEGACY_7_HELP">
			<Text>+75% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM">
			<Text>Sabum Kibitum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM_HELP">
			<Text>Front-line Unit which grows more powerful with experience. Only Babylon may build it. This unit is stronger than the Spearman it replaces. Receives additional [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength for every few levels and gains more XP from fights.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM_STRATEGY">
			<Text>A soldier to stand the test of time. The Kibitum is not the strongest unit in its era, but its true strength lies in how it gains more power from experience than normal units. Keep these soldiers alive, and they will form an indispensable core for your army.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BABYLON_KIBITUM_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Babylonians were descended from semi-nomadic Amorite and Akkadian tribes from upper Mesopotamia. With the collapse of the Sumerian and Akkadian kingdoms, these Amorite tribes poured into Mesopotamia unopposed and established new dynasties. While in many respects these conquerors assimilated into Sumerian culture, their armies retained the toughness of their nomadic roots.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Sabum Kibitum were the heavy troops of the Babylonians and one of the earliest examples of career soldiers in history. Assembled from the royal guard and city residents, Sabum Kibitum were armed with long and short spears, javelins and bows to form a disciplined and flexible fighting force.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Kibbutz -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KIBBUTZ">
			<Text>Kibbutz</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KIBBUTZ_HELP">
			<Text>Only Israel may build it. May only be built on farms and never adjacent to another Kibbutz. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to adjacent Farms and Great Person Tile Improvements.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KIBBUTZ_TEXT">
			<Text>A kibbutz is a collective community in Israel that was traditionally based on agriculture. The first kibbutz, Degania, was established in 1909 by predominantly Russian and Eastern European Jewish farmers. Kibbutzim began as an outgrowth of the Bilu movement, a combination of socialism and Zionism set on the agricultural settlement of the Land of Israel in reaction to the Russian Jewish Pogroms.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Today, farming has been partly supplanted by other economies, including industrial plants and high-tech enterprises. In recent decades, some kibbutzim have been privatized and changes have been made in the communal lifestyle. There were 270 kibbutzim in Israel as of 2010; their factories and farms account for 9% of Israel’s industrial, and 40% of its agricultural output, worth over 9.7 billion USD. Some Kibbutzim have developed high-tech and military industries, including military plastics and ammunition.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May only be built on farms and never adjacent to another Kibbutz. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to adjacent Farms and Great Person Tile Improvements.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KIBBUTZ">
			<Text>Establish a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_KIBBUTZ]Kibbutz[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KIBBUTZ_HELP">
			<Text>Only Israel may build it. May only be built on farms and never adjacent to another Kibbutz. Provides Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. [NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to adjacent Farms and Great Person Tile Improvements.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KIBBUTZ_REC">
			<Text>Establishing a Kibbutz will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture!</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Klepht -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PHILHELLENISM">
			<Text>Philhellenism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PHILHELLENISM_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every City-State Ally or Friend on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Attack[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT">
			<Text>Klepht</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT_HELP">
			<Text>A quick and elusive guerilla fighter. Only Greece may build it. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Philhellenism[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Commando[ENDCOLOR] Promotions, and can move after attacking.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>While not an effective front-line force, The Klepht can move quickly through enemy positions and strike at vulnerable back line units. This unit also gains gold and production for every city-state ally every time it attacks a unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREECE_KLEPHT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Bandits and mountainfolk, turned anti-Ottoman insurgents and freedom fighters, The Klephts were the bedrock upon which the modern Greek army was formed. Together with the men originally hired to capture them, the Armatoloi, the Klephts formed the "yeast of liberty", the first hope for Greek independence after more than four centuries of Ottoman rule.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Undisciplined and flighty as one would expect of brigands, Klephts waged an effective guerilla campaign against the much larger Ottoman armies sent to subdue them.  Massacres on both sides of the conflict were inflicted, but European sympathies fell heavily in favor of the Greeks. The unbridled cruelty of the Muslim Ottomans outraged Europe’s citizenry, who raised supplies, food and volunteers to fight for a Hellenic independence.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				After 8 years, Ottoman forces had finally managed to crush the revolt, but where Greek soldiers had failed poets and propaganda had succeeded. French, British, and Russian governments each sent a fleet in defense of the Greek islands in response to popular demand for intervention. In the face of such overwhelming force, the Ottomans sued for peace and liberated Greece. After more than 2,000 years under the boots of Macedonian, Roman and Ottoman conquerors, The Greek homeland was at last free -- unified as one people for the first time in history.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Kobukseon -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_KOREA_DECK_SPIKES">
			<Text>Deck Spikes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_KOREA_DECK_SPIKES_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Naval Melee Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Kraal -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ZULU_KRAAL">
			<Text>Isibaya</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ZULU_KRAAL_TEXT">
			<Text>An Isibaya is a Zulu homestead and defensive structure. The Isibaya is laid out in a circular pattern with a cattle enclosure at the centre, ringed by huts, palisades, and mud walls. The layout and function are reminiscent of a European corral, hence the Afrikaans term for Amabaya, "Kraal".[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Cattle were central to the life and economy of the Zulu Kingdom. Cattle were a sign of status, wealth, and power, and were instrumental for feeding and arming the amabutho regiments of the Zulu army.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Isibaya is a unique Zulu Great Person Tile Improvement, replacing the Citadel. It Provides [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and gives +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to adjacent Pastures.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building an Isibaya places a [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle Resource and claims adjacent tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Units standing on an Isibaya receive +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Tile Defense. Deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ZULU_KRAAL_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Zulu Great Person Tile Improvement, replacing the Citadel. Provides [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. Adjacent Pastures receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building an Isibaya places a [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle Resource and claims adjacent tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Units standing on an Isibaya receive +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Tile Defense. Deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ZULU_KRAAL">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ZULU_KRAAL]Isibaya[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ZULU_KRAAL_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs an Isibaya, which will increase [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and give +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to Adjacent Pastures. Gives +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units and deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units. Claims adjacent tiles and places a [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle Resource below the Isibaya.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ZULU_KRAAL_REC">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed.[NEWLINE]Unique Zulu Tile Improvement. [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. Adjacent Pastures receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Gives a [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus and damages adjacent Enemy Units. Claims adjacent tiles and places a [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle Resource below the Isibaya.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Lamassu Gate -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE">
			<Text>Lamassu Gate</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE_TEXT">
			<Text>Lamassu are Assyrian protective deities, often depicted as having a human head, the body of a bull or lion, and bird's wings. The Lamassu were household protective spirits of Babylonian and Assyrian commoners, and were later adopted as royal protectors. Depictions of Lamassu are found throughout Assyrian architecture, positioned as sentinels at the thresholds of buildings and as colossal statues on each side of the city and palace gates. Common folk, for their part, engraved Lamassi onto clay tablets and buried them under their doors' threshold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Wall replacement. Military Units supplied by this City's population increases by 20% and Increases the City's [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Bombard Strength by 30%. When training units in this city, 15% of their production cost is given as faith.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ASSYRIA_LAMASSU_GATE_HELP">
			<Text>[ICON_SILVER_FIST] Military Supplies by this City's population increased by 20%. Increases the City's [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Bombard Strength by 30% and Strike Range by 1. When you construct a Unit in this City, gain [ICON_PEACE] Faith equal to 15% of the Unit's [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production cost.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_CITY_STATE] Empire Size Modifier is reduced by 5% in this City.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Grenzer -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIA_LANDWEHR">
			<Text>Grenzer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIA_LANDWEHR_TEXT">
			<Text>The Habsburgs' military frontier were composed of a diverse array of client duchies, soldier-settlers, and refugees. These border-men, or Grenzers, developed a fearsome reputation for vigilance, tenacity, and fieldcraft after generations defending their lands from Ottoman raids. When the Muslim threat subsided in the 18th century, the Grenzers became a mainstay of Austro-Hungarian forces in their European conflicts, distinguishing themselves as flexible and reliable infantry in the Napoleonic Wars.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIA_LANDWEHR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Grenzer is the backbone of the Industrial-era Austrian army. It excels in defending in owned territory and the territory of allied city-states. Grenzers are slightly weaker than the Fusiliers they replace, but gain combat strength for each Diplomatic Marriage with your Empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AUSTRIA_LANDWEHR_HELP">
			<Text>Stalwart defensive Unit. Only Austria may build it. Has a [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Bonus when fighting in Territory owned by you or Allied City-States. When trained, gains additional Combat Strength for each [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Diplomatic Marriage[ENDCOLOR] on Empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Field Works[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AUSTRIA_YORKSCHER_MARCHE">
			<Text>Grenzer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AUSTRIA_YORKSCHER_MARCHE_HELP">
			<Text>Gains additional Combat Strength for each [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Diplomatic Marriage[ENDCOLOR] on Empire. [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lost on Upgrade[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Krupp Gun -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GERMANY_KRUPP_GUN">
			<Text>Krupp Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GERMANY_KRUPP_GUN_TEXT">
			<Text>A Krupp Gun is any member of a family of artillery pieces created by the Krupp family commercial steelworks, based in Essen. The Krupp Guns were the first cast steel field guns to enter mass production and adoption by any military, with the Royal Prussian Army's first purchase in 1856. Krupp Guns were renowned for their quality and for being at the forefront of new developments in artillery.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]At the outbreak of World War I, the German army doctrine emphasized mobility and the use of howitzer guns which fired in higher arcs to hit entrenched enemies at steeper angles. This doctrine paid early dividends during the initial stages of the Schlieffen Plan, where smaller, lighter German guns worked well as they marched through Belgium and Northern France, and raced the British to the sea. Though the bulk of their artillery was smaller pieces, like the 7.7 cm FK 96, the Germans also had some of the most impressive heavy artillery of the war with the Minenwerfers, or "mine throwers", short range artillery that outperformed contemporary mortars at a fraction of the weight. As the war began, Germany deployed twelve experimental 45 cm minenwerfer siege guns, some of the largest field artillery pieces ever produced. Affectionately dubbed "Big Bertha" by the German troops, these siege guns punched through dozens of hardened fortresses around Liege and Mauberge, taking the German army within striking distance of Paris in a matter of weeks.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GERMANY_KRUPP_GUN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Krupp Gun is an aggressive siege unit, specializing in breaking enemy defenses and bringing overwhelming firepower to bear. If a Krupp Gun manages to kill a unit stationed on top of a defensive tile improvement like a Fort or Citadel, the tile automatically becomes pillaged. Every Krupp Gun that attacks starts a thundering barrage, strengthening the attacks of every other Krupp Gun that also attacks that turn. Create an overwhelming force of artillery and smash the defenses of any civilization that stands against you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GERMANY_KRUPP_GUN_HELP">
			<Text>Siege unit adept at destroying fortified positions. Only Germany may build it.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]If this unit kills an enemy unit stationed on a defensive tile improvement, the tile is pillaged instantly. Gains more [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength for every Krupp Gun that has attacked in the same turn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Cover I[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_MINENWERFER">
			<Text>Minenwerfer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_MINENWERFER_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength when attacking [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fortified Units[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]Enemy Tile Improvements that provide [ICON_STRENGTH] Tile Defense are instantly pillaged if you [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]kill a unit on that tile[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER">
			<Text>Trommelfeuer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_00">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 0%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_01">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 5%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_02">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 10%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_03">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 15%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_04">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 20%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_05">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 25%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_06">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 30%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_07">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 35%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_08">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 40%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_09">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 45%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GERMANY_TROMMELFEUER_HELP_10">
			<Text>Gains +5% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Attack Strength this Turn whenever any unit with this promotion attacks on your turn (max of +50%)[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Current attack bonus:[ENDCOLOR] 50%</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Langskib -->
		<!-- Created by De_Genius on 28/10/2017, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo on 21/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB">
			<Text>Longship</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB_HELP">
			<Text>Early Naval Exploration Unit. Only Denmark may build it. Available earlier, can move after attacking, and has [COLOR_GREEN]Blockade[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Danish Longship is an early ship unit which allow Denmark to have early sea control. This allows Denmark to begin scouting the far seas earlier than the other players to prepare future waves of colonization, defend your colonies abroad and provides support to raids with its bonuses to city attack at sea and performing hit-and-run tactics.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DENMARK_LANGSKIB_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Longships were a type of boat invented and used by the Norsemen for trade, exploration, and warfare during the Viking Age. The longship's design evolved over many centuries, beginning in the Stone Age with the invention of the umiak and continuing up until the 6th century with clinker-built ships like Nydam and Kvalsund, appearing in its complete form between the 9th and 13th centuries. They were all made out of wood, with woven wool sails, and had numerous details and carvings on the hull.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Longships were notable for their quick speed and light construction. The ships were sturdy and reliable at sea, yet light enough to be carried onto shore or even tipped over as a makeshift shelter. The ability to move quickly in and out of shore was invaluable during the Vikings’ infamous raids.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The character and appearance of these ships are still reflected in Scandinavian boat-building traditions. Skills and methods for making longships are still used worldwide, often with modern adaptations
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION">
			<Text>Viking Exploration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Embarked Units[ENDCOLOR] starting in the same tile as a unit with this promotion [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can cross Ocean[ENDCOLOR]. Promotion stays until Embarked Unit leaves the Ocean.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION_CAN_CROSS_OCEAN">
			<Text>Free to Explore</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_DENMARK_VIKING_EXPLORATION_CAN_CROSS_OCEAN_HELP">
			<Text>Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can cross Ocean Tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>		

		<!-- Legion (lua code in Ballista.lua)-->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_ON_LEGION">
			<Text>Praefectus Castrorum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_ON_LEGION_HELP">
			<Text>+60% [ICON_WORKER] Work Rate if the unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]starts its turn near a Great General[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_EFFECT">
			<Text>Camp Management</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ROME_PRAEFECTUS_CASTRORUM_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>+60% [ICON_WORKER] Work Rate [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Great General[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Licorne -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 26/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_RUSSIA_GRAPESHOT">
			<Text>Grapeshot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_RUSSIA_GRAPESHOT_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Melee and Gunpowder Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE">
			<Text>Licorne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE_HELP">
			<Text>Highly mobile Siege Unit. Only Russia may build it. This Unit is available earlier, has better mobility in Enemy Territory, and can move after attacking. Very effective against enemy Melee and Gunpowder Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Licorne is a siege unit that can change the course of battle. Innovative construction allows moving after attacks and no penalty while attacking melee units. Is available earlier than the Field Gun.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_RUSSIA_LICORNE_TEXT">
			<Text>Licorne is the French name given to the Russian 'unicorn' cannons, named for the distinctively shaped handles on the gun barrels. Devised in 1757, Licornes were a flexible design, easy to fire and transport and made in many differing weights and power. Lighter designs are best remembered from their use as mobile horse artillery, a Russian innovation that would change the European theory of combined arms for the next century.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Longbowman -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 6/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ENGLAND_AGINCOURT">
			<Text>Agincourt</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ENGLAND_AGINCOURT_HELP">
			<Text>+20% [ICON_RANGED_STRENGTH] Attack Bonus and +20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Armor and Mounted Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Mamluk -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan, incorporated and modified by pineappledan on 17/07/2020 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPT_MAMLUK">
			<Text>Mamluk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPT_MAMLUK_TEXT">
			<Text>The Mamluks were a military knightly caste composed of slave-soldiers captured as young boys and sold into the Arabic world to serve as retainers. Because of their slave status ('Mamluk' directly translates to possession), these young men were dependent on their lord for social status and career advancement, making them reliable and dependable institutions in the Fatimid and Ayyubid dynasties of Cairo. The Mamluks were renowned warriors for their defense of Islam from waves of Crusader and Mongol invasions. In some cases, the Mamluks rose up and secured their own dynasties, initiating sultanates in Egypt, India, and Iraq.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPT_MAMLUK_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Mamluk is the unique Egyptian replacement for the Lancer. It is a strong mid-game unit that has advantages harrassing enemy positions, especially in open terrain. The Mamluk also reduces enemy religious spread while stationed inside.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EGYPT_MAMLUK_HELP">
			<Text>Agile Unit of the Renaissance Era. Only Egypt may build it. Deals increased damage against lightly and undamaged Units. Recovers Movement after attacks.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Mamluks stationed in cities reduce foreign Missionary and Prophet spread power by 50%.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_VUR_HA">
			<Text>Vur Ha!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_EGYPT_VUR_HA_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Units above 50 HP[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Move whenever this unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Attacks[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Marae -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_MARAE">
			<Text>Marae</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_MARAE_HELP">
			<Text>+5 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science whenever a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in this City, scaling with Era. +3 [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture whenever a Building is Constructed in this City, scaling with Era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_MARAE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Council replacement for the Polynesians. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Council, the Marae provides Gold, Food and Culture whenever a building is constructed in the city. Build the Marae as a first priority to maximize the bonuses for all later buildings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLYNESIA_MARAE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A Marae (or Malea) is a communal, sacred space in most Polynesian cultures. The Marae usually takes the form of a clearing, sometimes bordered with stones or posts, and sometimes with an accompanying shelter behind it. In most Polynesian cultures, the function of the Marae declined or disappeared with the arrival of Christianity, but it has retained its communal and cultural significance with the Maori of present-day New Zealand. 
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Monitor -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AMERICA_MONITOR">
			<Text>Harbor Defense</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AMERICA_MONITOR_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to adjacent Friendly Cities[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AMERICA_HARDENED">
			<Text>Hardened</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AMERICA_HARDENED_HELP">
			<Text>All incoming damage is reduced by 3.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Monolithic Church -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 12/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH">
			<Text>Monolithic Church</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The term "Monolithic Church" (or "rock-hewn church") can be attributed to any church cut from a single stone formation, but is most often used to refer to the complex of 11 churches in Lalibela, Ethiopia. These churches were constructed in the 12th century by King Gebre Mesqel Lalibela, a devout Christian. This 'New Jerusalem' is situated in a mountainous region in the heart of Ethiopia, and is an important center of Christian pilgrimage to this day.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Monolithic Churches are found in places besides Lalibela, including many in Tigray. These churches were almost unknown to the outside world until Abba Tewelde Medhin Josief, a Catholic priest, announced the existence of over 120 rock-hewn churches, 90 of which were still in use. Over the next few years, the total of known churches was raised to 153.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Monolithic Churches can be built on [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone, and on Hills with no resources and not next to another Monolithic Church.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Instead of Technologies, Monolithic Churches are improved by completing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Social Policy Branches[ENDCOLOR] and adopting an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ideology[ENDCOLOR] or [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Religious Beliefs[ENDCOLOR]:[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] for every Ancient Policy Branch,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PEACE] for every Medieval Policy Branch,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] for every Industrial Policy Branch,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PEACE] for adopting a Pantheon,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_PRODUCTION] for founding a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_PRODUCTION] for enhancing a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_GOLD] for reforming a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+2 [ICON_GOLD] for adopting an Ideology.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP">
			<Text>
				Can be built on [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone, and on Hills with no resources and not next to another Monolithic Church.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Instead of Technologies, Monolithic Churches are improved by completing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Social Policy Branches[ENDCOLOR] and adopting an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ideology[ENDCOLOR] or [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Religious Beliefs[ENDCOLOR]:[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] for every Ancient Policy Branch,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PEACE] for every Medieval Policy Branch,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] for every Industrial Policy Branch,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PEACE] for adopting a Pantheon,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] for founding a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_PRODUCTION] for enhancing a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_GOLD] and [ICON_PRODUCTION] for reforming a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+2 [ICON_GOLD] for adopting an Ideology.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH]Monolithic Church[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Monolithic Church, which increases [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Monolithic Churches increase yields when you adopt more Policies and Beliefs.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Nalanda -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NALANDA">
			<Text>Nalanda</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NALANDA_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Military Supply from Population in this City. Contains a prebuilt [ICON_VP_GREATWRITING] Great Work of Writing in one of the [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work slots. All owned Amphitheaters gain +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_CULTURE] Boredom in this City. +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Themed[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_NALANDA_TEXT">
			<Text>The mahavihara of Nalanda was a complex of monasteries, libraries, observatories, and amphitheatres spanning 30 acres in modern day Bihar, in Eastern India. One of the earliest institutions that could properly be considered a university, Nalanda boasted a curriculum that included philosophy, epistemology, theology, medicine, mathematics, astrology, and alchemy. In addition to its educational role, Nalanda hosted some of the most influential thinkers and lecturers of the Buddhist world for over 7 centuries, and attracted visiting scholars from across Asia. The university survived the fall of the Gupta Empire in the 6th century, and gained powerful patrons with the rise of the Pala Empire, but came to a violent end with the Muslim invasion of India. Archeological evidence suggests that Islamic invaders sacked Nalanda 3 separate times, the monks and scholars either killed or forced to flee. The national government of India has committed to founding a new Nalanda as a modern university near the ruins of the old compound. The revived Nalanda University accepted its first class of students in 2020.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_NALANDA_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"The rain could turn to gold, and still your thirst would not be slaked. Desire is unquenchable or it ends in tears."[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB] - Siddhartha Gautama[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_BUILDING_NALANDA">
			<Text>Dharmaganja</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NALANDA_THEMING_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure both Great Works were created by you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_WORK_BODHISATTVACARYAVATARA">
			<Text>The Way of the Bodhisattva</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GREAT_WORK_QUOTE_BODHISATTVACARYAVATARA">
			<Text>"We are the authors of our own destiny;[NEWLINE]and being the authors, we are ultimately, perhaps frighteningly,[NEWLINE]free."</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Nilometer -->
		<!-- Created by BlueGhost, incorporated and modified by adan_eslavo on 7/01/2018 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EGYPT_NILOMETER">
			<Text>Nilometer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EGYPT_NILOMETER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Egyptian replacement for both the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WELL} and the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WATERMILL}. It further increases the City's [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production output, especially during Golden Ages, and boosts river tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EGYPT_NILOMETER_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 5 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. +10% [ICON_FOOD] Food during [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Ages. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food from River tiles worked by this City.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Oppidum -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>Oppidum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM_HELP">
			<Text>
				Unique Celtic Great Tile Improvement. Can be built by Great Engineers, Merchants, Scientists, and Generals. Cannot be built next to another Oppidum.[NEWLINE]Improves Strategic Resources. Provides various yields and +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to Units stationed on it. Improves Adjacent Tile Improvements:[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_FOOD] and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] to Farms,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_FOOD] and +1 [ICON_PEACE] to Camps,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] and +1 [ICON_PEACE] to Pastures,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] and +1 [ICON_GOLD] to Mines,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] to Quarries,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_GOLD] and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] to Plantations,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_FOOD] and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] to Lumber mills,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_GOLD] and +1 [ICON_PEACE] to Fishing Boats.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Oppidum on Empire increases the effectiveness of the Hurry Production action of [ICON_GREAT_ENGINEER] Great Engineers, the Discover Technology action of [ICON_GREAT_SCIENTIST] Great Scientists, and the length of [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] 'We Love the King' Days from Trade Missions conducted by [ICON_GREAT_MERCHANT] Great Merchants.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM_TEXT">
			<Text>
				An Oppidum is a large defended settlement associated with the late La Tene culture. These fortified villages were often built in naturally protected areas and full of circular constructions. In times of conflict, the people who lived in open fields moved to these strategically located compounds to ensure their safety. Oppida could also have other purposes such as control of territory or safeguarding of crops. The most famous oppidum was Alesia, the site of the battle between Julius Caesar and Vercingetorix and the final defeat of the Gauls, ending of Gallic independence in France and Belgium.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Oppida can be built by Great Engineers, Merchants, Scientists, and Generals. They cannot be built next to each other. Each oppidum Gives +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it. They also improve the yields of adjacent improvements:[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to Farms[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith to Camps[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith  to Pastures[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to Mines[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to Quarries[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to Plantations[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to Lumber Mills[NEWLINE]
				[ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith to Fishing Boats
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CELTS_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM]Oppidum[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CELTS_OPPIDUM_HELP">
			<Text>
				Cannot be built next to another Oppidum.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It will increase [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All Yields[ENDCOLOR]. Gives +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it. Provides bonus yields to most non-road and non-great person Improvements:[NEWLINE]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CELTS_OPPIDUM_REC">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed[NEWLINE]Unique Celtic Great Tile Improvement. Will connect Strategic Resources on this tile to the trade network. Gives a [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it. Adjacent Improvements gain additional bonus yields.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Otomi -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_OTOMI">
			<Text>Otomi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_OTOMI_TEXT">
			<Text>The Otomi are an ancient people from the Altiplano region, predate the Mexica's arrival there by thousands of years. The name Otomi is Nahuatl, meaning "One who walks with Arrows" in recognition of their strength and bravery in combat. Within the Triple-Alliance, Otomi became a name for a military society, perhaps because of the fearsome reputation of the Otomi people or because they were originally comprised of Otomi allies and mercenaries. Whatever the case, the use of Otomi both as the name of an ethnicity within the Aztec Empire and as a military faction makes it hard to discern which is which in the historical record.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_OTOMI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Otomi is the unique Aztec replacement for the Warrior and is thus available right from the start of the game. It has enhanced movement in Forest and Jungle, and has enhanced defense and healing outside friendly lands. Unlike regular Warriors, the Otomi's bonus against Barbarians is retained on upgrade, allowing them to efficiently deal with Barbarian threats even after upgraded to Spearmen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AZTEC_OTOMI_HELP">
			<Text>Strong, front-line Unit of the Ancient Era. Only the Aztecs may build it. Deals significantly more damage against Barbarian units. Starts with [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_WOODSMAN}[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SURVIVALISM_1}[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CAPTIVES_OF_WAR">
			<Text>War Captives</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_CAPTIVES_OF_WAR_HELP">
			<Text>+30% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Units at or below 50 HP[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_BRUTE_STRENGTH">
			<Text>Brute Strength</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_AZTEC_BRUTE_STRENGTH_HELP">
			<Text>+40% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Barbarians[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Pitz -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 16/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_0">
			<Text>K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_0_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gets unique ability [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]every 20 Game Turns[ENDCOLOR]. Effect can be extended [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]4[ENDCOLOR] times.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_1">
			<Text>Hun K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_1_HELP">
			<Text>+5 XP.[NEWLINE]+5% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength and +5% [ICON_DEFENSE] Attack [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_2">
			<Text>Ka'a K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_2_HELP">
			<Text>+5 XP.[NEWLINE]+10% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength and +10% [ICON_DEFENSE] Attack [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_3">
			<Text>Oox K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_3_HELP">
			<Text>+5 XP.[NEWLINE]+15% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength and +15% [ICON_DEFENSE] Attack [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_4">
			<Text>Kan K'atun Ahaw</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_MAYA_KATUN_AHAW_4_HELP">
			<Text>+10 XP.[NEWLINE]+15% [ICON_DEFENSE] Combat Strength and +15% [ICON_DEFENSE] Attack and Double Healing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in Forest and Jungle[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ">
			<Text>Pitz Court</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ_HELP">
			<Text>Barracks, Forge, and Armory in this City gain +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_CULTURE] Boredom. +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism for every 4 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Grants [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_PEACE] Faith at the end of every Long Count. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Land Units trained in this City receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]K'atun Ahaw[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, which grants new abilities for every 20 turns the Unit has been alive.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_PERFUME] Perfume: +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_OLIVE] Olives: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Pitz Court is the Mayan unique building, replacing the Arena. In addition to the normal bonuses of an Arena, the Pitz Court provides Science and Faith at the end of every long count. Land units trained in a City with a Pitz Court receive the 'K'atun Ahaw' promotion, which grants new abilities for every 20 turns the unit has been alive.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Hun: 5XP, +5% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Ka'a: 10XP, +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength, +5% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength in Forest/Jungle
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Oox: 10XP, +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength, +15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength in Forest/Jungle
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Kan: 15XP, +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength, +15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength in Forest/Jungle, +10 HP on Heal in Friendly Territory.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAYA_PITZ_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Mesoamerican Ball Game, or 'Pitz', is a game of ritual and cultural significance among the Mayan people. The object of the game is to keep the ball in play for as long as possible by striking back and forth within a sloped arena using the hips, though some variations allowed for elbows, shoulders and even rackets. The earliest archaeological evidence of the game come from a court estimated to be 3400 years old.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Over 1300 different ballcourts have been found within Mayan ruins, with relatively little variation in size or layout over thousands of years. Every court is shaped as a narrow alley with gently sloping walls on either side and enclosed endzones. This gave the court a roughly H-shaped layout. Later versions of the ballcourts would include hoops at the midpoint, suspended on the walls. Actually sending a ball through the ring must have been a rare occurrence, since the players could not use their hands or feet to guide the ball. Moreover, the rings were only slightly larger than the ball itself and were a long way from the playing alley.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The game was more than a mere sporting event to the Mayan people, serving as a substitute for war in the case of a dispute between cities. Later Classical Mayan art suggests a link between the ball game and ritual sacrifice, with winners being decapitated as an offering to the gods. The Maya Twin Myth of the Popol Vuh describes the game between the Hero Twins, Hunahpu and Xbalanque, and lords of the underworld, One Death and Seven Death. The game was played so the Hero Twins might recover Hunahpu's head, which was being used as a ball by the Lords (Hunahpu had been using a squash for his head until his real one could be recovered).
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Pancerny -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 16/10/2017 modified 30/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BOGURODZICA">
			<Text>Bogurodzica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_POLAND_BOGURODZICA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_PEACE] Faith [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Kill[ENDCOLOR]. Bonus doubled [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Barbarian Kills[ENDCOLOR]. +25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY">
			<Text>Pancerny</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY_HELP">
			<Text>A sturdy Mounted Skirmisher. Only Poland may build it. Earns [ICON_PEACE] Faith from each Enemy killed and double the amount from Barbarians. This Unit is stronger in both defense and offense than the Heavy Skirmisher, and has additional protection against Ranged Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Pancerny is the Polish replacement for the Heavy Skirmisher. It has stronger attack and defense than the Heavy Skirmisher, and takes reduced damage from Ranged attacks. The Pancerny also earns Faith for each enemy killed. As mounted unit, the Pancerny is vulnerable to Pikemen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLAND_PANCERNY_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Towarzysz Pancerny (Mailed Companion) was a rank of Polish cavalryman from the 10th to 18th century, named for their chainmail armor. Pancerni were organized into companies, with each company consisting of 60 to 200 horsemen. Exceptionally well-armored, they used chainmail or platemail armor, vambraces, helmets, and buckler shields. The most common armaments were sabres, reflex bows and, with the arrival of gunpowder, flintlock pistols and carbines.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				After the rise of heavy cavalry the Pancerni often worked in concert with the newer and more heavily armed husaria, augmenting a cavalry charge and chasing down routing enemy soldiers. By the second half of the 17th century, they represented approximately 70% of all soldiers in the Polish military, fighting against Cossacks, Tatars, and the Swedish. The Husaria and Pancerni were eventually combined to form the ‘Kawaleria Narodowa’, the Polish-Lithuanian National Cavalry.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Parthenon -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PARTHENON_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Parthenon is the Greek Unique Wonder, replacing the Scrivener's Office. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Scrivener's Office, the Parthenon gives additional production to diplomatic units, more paper, and more free diplomatic units. The Parthenon also gives all your diplomatic units the Proxenos promotion, which gives permanent gold to the Parthenon when they complete diplomatic missions. With the Parthenon, Greece can secure a safe source of income in addition to competing for the favour and benefits of City-State Allies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PROXENOS">
			<Text>Proxenos</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_GREECE_PROXENOS_HELP">
			<Text>+5 [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold permanently in the [ICON_CAPITAL]Capital on completion of a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Diplomatic Mission in City-State's territory[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Pogost -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 14/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_1">
			<Text>Pogost</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_1_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to Villages and Towns. Incoming [ICON_ARROW_LEFT] Trade Routes generate +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for the City, and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Trade Route owner. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_GOLD] Poverty.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gains additional yields upon the discovery of new Technologies:[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science at [COLOR_CYAN]Banking[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_FOOD] Food at [COLOR_CYAN]Economics[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production at [COLOR_CYAN]Railroad[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]+1 to [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]All Yields[ENDCOLOR] at [COLOR_CYAN]Industrialization[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_BANANA] Bananas: +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COFFEE] Coffee: +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_TEA] Tea: +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold, +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_TOBACCO] Tobacco: +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Russian replacement for the Customs House. In addition to the bonuses of a Customs House, the Pogost increases the yields of all nearby Villages. The Pogost also gains significantly more base yields as you progress through the technology tree.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUSSIA_POGOST_TEXT">
			<Text>The Pogost as an institution of Russian rural life existed for nearly a millenium, and in that time it underwent multiple transformations. In many medieval Russian states, Pogosts began as inns and lodging for the nobility and priesthood, but may have doubled as community centers and trading hubs. By the end of the 10th century, however, Pogosts had evolved into administrative and legislative hubs throughout the Slavic states. By 1775 the last Pogost-led administrative district was abolished, and the buildings were repurposed as parishes of the Eastern Orthodox Church.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Penteconter -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 30/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER">
			<Text>Penteconter</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER_HELP">
			<Text>Dominant Classical Era Naval Unit used to own the seas well into the Medieval Era with its ranged attack.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The first naval unit with a ranged attack. It cannot end its turn in Deep Ocean tiles outside of the city borders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PENTECONTER_TEXT">
			<Text>The penteconter was an ancient Greek Galley, used for trade, piracy and warfare. The ship was rowed by 50 oarsmen arranged in 2 rows of 25, making the ship long, but relatively narrow. This design made the boat relatively quick, but difficult to turn during a naval engagement.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Pracinha -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BRAZIL_EXPEDITIONARY_FORCE">
			<Text>Expeditionary Force</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BRAZIL_EXPEDITIONARY_FORCE_HELP">
			<Text>+1% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]for every tile between unit and [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BRAZIL_TOURISM">
			<Text>Glorious Banner</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_BRAZIL_TOURISM_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]toward all Civilizations on Kill[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Prowler -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 20/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER">
			<Text>Prowler</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER_HELP">
			<Text>A nimble attacker excelling in Rough Terrain. Only the Iroquois may build it. Cheaper than the Musketman, this Unit can attack from behind obstacles and withdraw from enemy attacks.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Prowler is a cheap unit that makes perfect use of surrounding rough terrain. The Prowler's "Indirect Fire" promotion allows him to attack unseen from deep forests and hills, with the aid of reconnaissance or friendly borders. When attacked by an enemy unit, he can withdraw from combat. The prowler's evasiveness makes him an ideal guerilla Unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_PROWLER_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Unlike many other tribes, the Iroquois had easy access to trade goods at Dutch forts along the Hudson River, and traded for various goods and luxuries. Weapons of war such as the iron axe and musket were highly sought after, and by the 1640s the Iroquois were well-equipped to fight their traditional Huron and Algonquian enemies. Common muskets were given in exchange for pelts and food, but often of lighter and smaller caliber than military-grade muskets. The Dutch and British feared giving high-quality weapons to people who could turn against them, but the Iroquois often found the smaller weapons more suitable to rough terrain anyways.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				War tactics were changed after the Iroquois' acquisition of firearms. The lethality of their new weapons put the Iroquois, never a highly populous group, in a precarious position. The tribes' custom of absorbing refugees and prisoners of war changed as fewer and fewer warriors survived clashes with European arms. Great armies walking with prominent chiefs and shamans were replaced with guerilla tactics, small bands of troops guided by commanders.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Qizilbash -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 29/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PERSIA_SAFAVI_AGITATOR">
			<Text>Safavi Agitator</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PERSIA_SAFAVI_AGITATOR_HELP">
			<Text>Unit gains [ICON_PEACE] Faith, [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points when [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Pillaging Tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH">
			<Text>Qizilbash</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH_HELP">
			<Text>Potent Mid-game cavalry focused on economic warfare. Only Persia may build it. Can always be purchased with [ICON_PEACE] Faith.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Generates [ICON_PEACE] Faith, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points when pillaging tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Qizilbash is the Unique Persian replacement for the Lancer. Stronger than the Lancer, the Qizilbash also generates Faith, Gold and Golden Age Points for every tile they pillage. This unit can also be purchased with Faith without needing a religious tenet. Maintaining a strong presence in enemy territory allows Persia to generate Faith for more Qizilbash, and trigger more Golden Ages to increase your army's power.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PERSIA_QIZILBASH_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Qizilbash (Tr: “red-heads”) was originally a pejorative for the followers of the Safawiyyah Sufi order. Named for their distinctive crimson headwear, the Qizilbash organized into a Shi'ite society reminiscent of a European knightly order. Though primarily of Turkman origin, the Qizilbash proved instrumental in the establishment of the Iranian Safavid Dynasty.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				In a campaign to avenge the death of his father, Ismail I led 7000 Qizilbash warriors to victory over an Aq Qoyunlu force of 30 000, and established the Safavid State. Within eleven short years, Ismail brought all of Iran under his control, becoming the first ethnically Iranian monarch to unify Iran in over 850 years. Though they had made him a powerful king, Ismail feared the influence of the Qizilbash over the Iranian people. Ismail and his successors would spend the next 80 years diminishing the threat posed by the foreign Qizilbash, replacing them with slave soldiers from the Caucasus. Nevertheless, the Qizilbash maintained a place of honor within the Safavid Empire, both on the battlefield and at court.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Qila -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 5/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA">
			<Text>Qila</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA_HELP">
			<Text>Damage from all sources against this City is reduced by 2. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for Quarries worked by this City. Contains 1 slot for a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Art or Artifact.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_STRENGTH] City Strength for every 2 National or World Wonders built in the City. 20% of [ICON_STRENGTH] City Defense is converted into [ICON_CULTURE] Culture every turn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_CITY_STATE] Empire Size Modifier is reduced by 5% in this City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Qila is the unique Indian replacement for the Castle. In addition to the normal bonuses of the Castle, the Qila generates Culture and Great Artist Points. 10% of City Defense is converted into Culture every turn and the city gains more defense for wonders built in the city. Your most magnificent cities also become more difficult to capture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDIA_QILA_TEXT">
			<Text>The Mughals were an Islamic empire that invaded India in the 15th century, and ruled most of the sub-continent until the mid 19th. During their rule, they constructed elaborate forts called Qila across the countryside which served as administrative centers and living quarters for the occupiers. These forts were beautiful structures, fitting palaces for the rulers of a vast empire. Several--including the magnificent "Lahore Fort" and Red Fort of Agra--survive today and remain as some of the largest tourist attractions to India, monuments to the Mughals' power and style.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Ranch -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH">
			<Text>Homestead</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH_TEXT">
			<Text>A Homestead is a complex of buildings on a large landholding, typically a ranch, settled in accordance with the United States Homesteading Acts. The US Government implemented a policy of "free soil", allowing claimants, effectively squatters, ownership of land which they had converted into productive farms or ranches. Nearly 10% of the continental United States was settled in this way; 270 million acres of land claimed by approximately 1.6 million homesteaders between 1862 and 1930.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The colonization of vast swathes of the continental interior left an indelible mark on the American psyche. Legends of the frontier, the Old West, Cowboys and Indians still permeate American culture, informing their sense of independence, enterprising spirit and mastery over nature.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Homestead is the American replacement for the Stable. In addition to the regular abilities of the Stable, the Homestead immediately claims all Sheep, Horse, Cattle and Bison resources around the City. The production bonus for each claimed tile can help refund a bit of the cost of the Homestead immediately. The Homestead boosts Bison in addition to all the resources normally boosted by a Stable, and all boosted resources gain additional food.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Homestead boosts the production of workers and settler units, and allows America to train Pioneers a full era before they usually unlock. With the Homestead, America can settle new, powerful cities quickly.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMERICA_RANCH_HELP">
			<Text>+33% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building Mounted Units and +25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building Worker and Settler units. Pioneers can be built in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Increases the [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Military Supply Cap from [ICON_CITIZEN] Population in the City by 10%. Gain 15 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production whenever a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born in the City, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]On completion, the city immediately claims all [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse, [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep, [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle, and [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison within 3 tiles of the City. The City gains 20 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for each tile claimed, scaling with Era. Internal [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes from this City generate +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses: +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep: +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle: +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison: +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Riad -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOROCCO_RIAD">
			<Text>Riad</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOROCCO_RIAD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A Riad is a traditional North African house built in a peristyle format, surrounding an interior garden or courtyard. These homes were often plain on the exterior, but lavishly decorated inside, projecting humility and austerity while preserving a family’s comfort and privacy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				While architectural style has changed over the years, the riad’s basic form is still used in modern design. Riads enjoyed something of a renaissance during French occupation of North Africa. As befitting Europe's fascination with preserving historic heritage sites, restoration efforts on old Riads were undertaken throughout Morocco's major cities, often converting old Riads into hotels or restaurants.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOROCCO_RIAD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Riad is the Moroccan unique replacement for the Hotel. In addition to the bonuses of the Hotel, The Riad gives substantial bonuses to culture and gold for each building already constructed in the city. It also increases in power for each new Era you enter. All purchases made in a city with a Riad generate tourism. Use your Riads to push for a cultural victory over your opponents.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOROCCO_RIAD_HELP">
			<Text>When completed, gains [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for every 8 Buildings and Wonders already constructed in this city. Gains +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture every Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When you spend [ICON_INVEST] Gold to purchase Units or invest in Buildings in this City, 10% of the cost is converted into [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]33% of the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from [ICON_WONDER] World Wonders and Tiles is added to the [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output of the City. [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output from Great Works +25%.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Tadodaho -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan 15/06/2023 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_IROQUOIS_DIPLOMATIC_RECIPROCITY">
			<Text>Reciprocity</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_IROQUOIS_DIPLOMATIC_RECIPROCITY_HELP">
			<Text>When Expended, the yields of the tile the Great Diplomat occupied are permanently added to your [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_TADODAHO">
			<Text>Tadodaho</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_TADODAHO_HELP">
			<Text>Receives [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Master Diplomat[ENDCOLOR] Promotion for free, which grants 100 [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence from Diplomatic Missions, plus additional [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence for each completed era. Also receives the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Reciprocity[ENDCOLOR] Promotion for free, which copies the yields of the tile the Great Diplomat occupied when expended and permanently adds them to your [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You may [ICON_MOVES] move this unit to a City-State you are not at war with and choose one of two options. First, you may conduct a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Diplomatic Mission[ENDCOLOR] to increase your [ICON_INFLUENCE] Resting Influence with the target City-State by 45, receive [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence and reduce the [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence of other Civilizations by the same amount. Second, you can construct an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Embassy[ENDCOLOR], which grants an additional vote in the World Congress. Either action expends the Tadodaho.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When expended, gain +1 [ICON_RES_PAPER] Paper. A free Tadodaho is born when you complete a [COLOR_MAGENTA]Policy Branch[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_TADODAHO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Tadodaho is a unique Iroquoian Great Diplomat replacement. Aside from the Great Diplomat's abilities, a Tadodaho has the Reciprocity ability, which copies the tile yields of an embassy the Tadodaho plants in City-State lands, and gives those yields to your capital. The Tadodaho also gives more resting influence when expended for a Diplomatic mission than the regular Great Diplomat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IROQUOIS_TADODAHO_TEXT">
			<Text>The Tadodaho, also called the Fire Keeper, refers to the head of the Grand Council of the Six Nations that includes the Cayuga, Mohawk, Oneida, Onondaga, Seneca, and Tuscarora people. A spiritual and political leader, the position dates back to the original founding of the Iroquois Confederacy; the hoyenah (chieftain) of the Onondaga Nation in the time of Hiawatha and the Great Peacemaker was named Tadodaho. The leadership of the Grand Council, and the honorific title of its founder, has been passed down for centuries, and is a lifetime appointment. It is said there have been 27 Tadodahos since the original founding of the Haudenosaunee (also called Iroquois) Confederacy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Great Council Fire of the Iroquois League is still located within the Onondaga reservation in present-day New York. The Tadodahos of recent history have continued to fight for the repatriation and preservation of Haudenosaunee culture, language, and history, as well as petition the American and Canadian governments in defense of their people's lands and treaty rights.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Salon -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 10/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_SALON">
			<Text>Salon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_SALON_HELP">
			<Text>Available much earlier. Does not require a Gallery. Allows [COLOR_YELLOW]Archaeologists[ENDCOLOR] to be built in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism for every 4 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works in the City produce +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]-1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_CULTURE] Boredom.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Can be [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Themed[ENDCOLOR] in 9 different arrangements. +5 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. +3 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and +10% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People generation for each active Theming bonus in the City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_SALON_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Salon is the French unique building, replacing the Museum. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Museum, The Salon also yields Science and increases Great People generation for each active theming bonus in the city.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_SALON_TEXT">
			<Text>A salon is a gathering of people under the roof of an inspiring host, held partly to amuse one another and partly to refine the taste and increase the knowledge of the participants through conversation. These gatherings often consciously followed Horace's definition of the aims of poetry, "either to please or to educate" ("aut delectare aut prodesse est"). Salons, commonly associated with French literary and philosophical movements of the 17th and 18th centuries, were carried on until quite recently in urban settings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_FRANCE_SALON_1">
			<Text>Cabinet de Curiosités</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_FRANCE_SALON_2">
			<Text>Collection Exotique</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_FRANCE_SALON_3">
			<Text>Ensemble de Diplômes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_FRANCE_SALON_4">
			<Text>Illustrations Architecturales</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_FRANCE_SALON_5">
			<Text>Galerie des Batailles</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_FRANCE_SALON_6">
			<Text>Retrospective Étrangère</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_FRANCE_SALON_7">
			<Text>Synesthésie Artistique</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_FRANCE_SALON_8">
			<Text>Salle de Marine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_FRANCE_SALON_9">
			<Text>Pièce des Voyages</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FRANCE_SALON_THEMING_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure the Great Work Slots are all filled with Great Art or Artifacts either all from your own Civilization or all from Civilizations other than your own.</Text>
		</Row>	
		<!-- Sambadrome -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRAZIL_SAMBADROME">
			<Text>Sambadrome</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRAZIL_SAMBADROME_TEXT">
			<Text>A Sambadrome is an exhibition place for the Samba schools parades during Carnaval in Brazil. A Sambadrome generally consists of tiered spectator viewing areas surrounding a long alley for the schools to parade down.  The parades attract many thousands of Brazilians and foreign tourists each year.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRAZIL_SAMBADROME_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Sambadrome is the unique Brazilian replacement for the Opera House. In addition to the bonuses of an Opera House, the Sambadrome also generates Golden Age Points. The Sambadrome comes with a Musician specialist slot, and all Musicians in the city generate extra Gold and Golden Age Points.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRAZIL_SAMBADROME_HELP">
			<Text>Unique replacement for the Opera House. +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City. 10% of [ICON_CULTURE] Culture created by the City counts as [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points Per Turn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works in the City produce +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism. +33% [ICON_GREAT_MUSICIAN] Great Musician Points in the City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contains 1 slot for [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Music.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Starts 10 turns of 'Carnaval' when completed.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Scythed Chariot -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 26/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHE">
			<Text>Rend</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHE_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]On Move[ENDCOLOR] inflicts 5 [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to all new adjacent Enemy Units[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lost on Upgrade[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_CARNYX">
			<Text>Carnyx</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CELTS_CARNYX_HELP">
			<Text>+10% [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Archer and Melee Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT">
			<Text>Scythed Chariot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_HELP">
			<Text>A dangerous Unit on Open Terrain. Only the Celts may build it. This unit is stronger against Archer and Melee Units.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After moving, deals damage to all newly adjacent Enemy Units, but has fewer moves and the [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Beam Axle[ENDCOLOR] movement penalty.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Scythed Chariot is a Celtic unique unit made for destroying enemy lines. The Scythed chariot is a continuation of the chariot line, with a powerful ranged attack, but it moves much slower than contemporary skirmishers, especially in rough terrain. Enemies take damage whenever the Scythed Chariot moves adjacent to them, making this unit deadly in open terrain. Make every move count to maximize damage, but be careful not to leave your Chariots exposed to enemies on their turn. A mounted unit, the Scythed Chariot is vulnerable to Spearmen.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CELTS_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Scythed chariots are modified war chariots with long blades extending from the wheel axels. Though often dismissed as fanciful storytelling, the use of scythed chariots has been ascribed to Pictish, Irish and Iceni armies. The only report of a scythed chariot in Britain outside of Roman propaganda comes from the Irish Ulster Cycle, during the adventures of Chu Chulainn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Although chariots had fallen out of use in continental Europe from the end of the 3rd century BC, Caesar found that they remained significant in British warfare. Caesar encountered both Celtic cavalry and chariots and described how these warriors would throw javelins from their vehicles before dismounting to fight on foot. Celtic soldiers could return to their chariots to quickly retreat or redeploy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				“They make war not only on horseback but also from two horse chariots and cars armed in the Gallic fashion – they call them Covinni - on which they use axles equipped with scythes.” [NEWLINE]
				- Pomponius Mela
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Seir Morb -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 9/12/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER">
			<Text>Crouching Tiger</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SIAM_CROACHING_TIGER_HELP">
			<Text>Attacks deal 15 Bonus Damage to all Units on the tile [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]if Unit has not moved this turn[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lost on Upgrade[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB">
			<Text>Seir Morb</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB_HELP">
			<Text>Industrial Era Unit specializing in coastal defense. Only Siam may build it. Has a bonus against Naval Units, but no bonuses against Cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Deals bonus damage on attack to all units and cities on a tile if the Seir Morb has not moved that turn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Cover I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB_STRATEGY">
			<Text>A powerful coastal defense cannon, the Seir Morb is more powerful than the Field Gun it replaces, especially against naval targets, but deals less damage to cities. The cannon deals 20 extra damage if it has not moved at all that turn, so pick a good spot and keep it steady. Bonus damage from movement affects all enemy units stacked on a tile, including garrisons inside cities and embarked units protected by naval units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SIAM_SEIR_MORB_TEXT">
			<Text>Despite Siam's remarkable diplomacy, they did occasionally come into conflict with the western imperial powers which threated their independence. When the French set their sights on Laos, the Siamese mistakenly believed the English would support them against France and prepared for war. The Seir Morb ("Crouching Tiger") were the most technologically advanced cannons in the Siamese arsenal at the time; coastal artillery which could destroy any French boats foolish enough to enter their harbours. However, no amount of raw power can account for corruption and disorganization; the French managed to establish their beachheads, and the coastal artillery of Thailand remained unused. It turns out that the finest artillery money can buy still needs to be fired.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Suffet -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET">
			<Text>Suffet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>This Carthaginian unique Great Person replaces the Great General. Aside from the ability to boost nearby troops and construct citadels, this unit disembarks onto water tiles as a [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral. Causes Friendly Units beginning in the same or adjacent tile to ignore Enemy Zone of Control for that turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Suffet is the unique Great General and Great Admiral replacement for Carthage. This unit causes all friendly units beginning in the same or an adjacent tile to ignore an enemy's Zone of Control for that turn. In addition, whenever this unit embarks into a water tile, it becomes a Great Admiral. It returns to Great General status upon disembarking into a city. Use a Suffet to enhance your military's power and mobility in pitched battles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>In the various independent city-states and colonies of Phoenicia a Suffet (or Shophet) was a non-royal magistrate granted control over a city-state, sometimes functioning much in the same way as a Roman consul. Following the overthrow of its monarchy in the 5th century BC, Carthage was ruled by a number of aristocratic councils presided over by two suffets. The exceptional leadership of suffet generals like Hannibal Barca have become legendary, handing Rome the greatest defeats it had ever suffered.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_GENERAL">
			<Text>Punic Commander</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_GENERAL_HELP">
			<Text>Unit turns into a [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Embark[ENDCOLOR]. [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]From the beginning of the turn to its end[ENDCOLOR], Friendly Units stacked or adjacent to the Suffet gain [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Plague Immunity[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]ignore Zone of Control[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_ADMIRAL">
			<Text>Punic Commander</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_ADMIRAL_HELP">
			<Text>Unit turns into a [ICON_GREAT_GENERAL] Great General if it [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]is standing in City[ENDCOLOR]. [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]From the beginning of the turn to its end[ENDCOLOR], Friendly Units stacked or adjacent to the Suffet gain [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Plague Immunity[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]ignore Zone of Control[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_ZOC">
			<Text>Cannae and Drepana</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CARTHAGE_ZOC_HELP">
			<Text>Unit has [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Plague Immunity[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]ignores Zone of Control[ENDCOLOR] for 1 turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Unique Names-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_1">
			<Text>Bomilcar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_2">
			<Text>Hamilcar Barca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_3">
			<Text>Hannibal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_4">
			<Text>Hannibal Barca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_5">
			<Text>Hasdrubal II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_6">
			<Text>Hasdrubal Gisco</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_7">
			<Text>Hasdrubal the Boetharch</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_8">
			<Text>Mago I Justin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_9">
			<Text>Mago II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_10">
			<Text>Mago III</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_11">
			<Text>Himilco I</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_12">
			<Text>Himilco II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_13">
			<Text>Hasdrubal the Fair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_14">
			<Text>Ad Herbal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_15">
			<Text>Carthalo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_16">
			<Text>Hannibal Monomachus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_17">
			<Text>Maharbal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_18">
			<Text>Sophonisba</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_19">
			<Text>Hannibal the Rhodian</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_20">
			<Text>Hanno the Elder</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_21">
			<Text>Hanno the Great</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_22">
			<Text>Aderbaal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_23">
			<Text>Bodashtart</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_24">
			<Text>Philosir</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CARTHAGE_SHOPHET_25">
			<Text>Abdmelqart</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Suffet -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET">
			<Text>Shofet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>This Israelite unique Great Person replaces the Great General. Aside from the ability to boost nearby troops and construct citadels, this unit generates +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_PEACE] Faith every turn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Deals damage every turn to enemy cities the Shofet is adjacent to. Damage is doubled if the city is [ICON_BLOCKADED] Blockaded</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Shofet is the unique Great General replacement for Israel. The Shofet is very effective at shortening sieges, dealing consistent damage each turn if adjacent to an enemy city. Shoftim also act as a steady supply of Faith and Culture for your Empire, so don't feel the need to build citadels with them right away.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>The Judges of Israel, or Shoftim, were Israelite military leaders in times of crisis, before Israel established their monarchy. The Book of Judges in the Hebrew Bible describes the Shofet as part of a cyclical pattern: The Israelite people fall away from their god, hardship is brought on as punishment from God, the Israelites cry out to the Lord for rescue, God sends a Shofet to lead the Israelites to overthrow their persecutors, and the cycle repeats. The cycle of Judges is thought to have gone on for between 300 and 500 years.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The first judge of Israel named by the Bible was Moses, who is said to have led the Israelites out of bondage in Egypt and established the Jewish law. After Moses, Joshua led the Israelites in the conquest of Canaan. The final judge named in the Bible was Samuel, who anointed both the first and second kings of the new Kingdom of Israel.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SHOPHET">
			<Text>Judge of Israel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SHOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith every turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SHOFAR">
			<Text>Ba'al Tekiah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SHOFAR_HELP">
			<Text>Deals 20 Damage to adjacent enemy City every turn. Effect is doubled if enemy City is [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Blockaded[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Unique Names-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_1">
			<Text>Joshua</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_2">
			<Text>Othniel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_3">
			<Text>Ehud</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_4">
			<Text>Shamgar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_5">
			<Text>Deborah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_6">
			<Text>Gideon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_7">
			<Text>Abimelech</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_8">
			<Text>Tola</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_9">
			<Text>Jair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_10">
			<Text>Jephthah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_11">
			<Text>Ibzan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_12">
			<Text>Elon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_13">
			<Text>Abdon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_14">
			<Text>Samson</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_15">
			<Text>Eli</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_16">
			<Text>Samuel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_17">
			<Text>Moses</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_18">
			<Text>Joel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_19">
			<Text>Abadiah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_20">
			<Text>Amariah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_21">
			<Text>Zebediah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_SHOPHET_22">
			<Text>Barak</Text>
		</Row>	
		<!-- Shotelai -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 12/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_0">
			<Text>Maim</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_0_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]After Attack[ENDCOLOR] Defending Enemy Unit is marked. Marked unit has reduced [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]next turn[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_1">
			<Text>Maimed</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_MAIM_1_HELP">
			<Text>-2 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_HOOKED_WEAPON">
			<Text>Shotelai</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_HOOKED_WEAPON_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength vs [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Mounted Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI">
			<Text>Chewa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI_HELP">
			<Text>Front-line Medieval Era land Unit. Only Ethiopia may build it. It is stronger against Mounted Units, unlike the Longswordsman it replaces. Enemies attacked by this Unit have -2 [ICON_MOVES] Movement Points on their next turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique replacement for the Longswordsman. This unit specializes in combating Mounted opponents and hobbling retreating units. Only Ethiopia may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ETHIOPIA_SHOTELAI_TEXT">
			<Text>Chewa were the noble warrior caste of Ethiopian medieval society, appointed by the emperor and furnished with land grants for their service. The Chewa nobility are famous for the use of the Shotel, a dramatically curved double-edged swords that are unique to the Ethiopian Empire. Almost semicircular, the shotel could be used to hook shields, or to reach around them to strike an opponent. The sword could also be used to hook and unhorse a mounted soldier, bringing them to the ground.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Sofa -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SONGHAI_HORSE_FATHER">
			<Text>Father of the Horse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SONGHAI_HORSE_FATHER_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]to all Friendly Mounted Units within 2 tiles[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SONGHAI_HORSE_FATHER_EFFECT">
			<Text>Nearby Sofa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SONGHAI_HORSE_FATHER_EFFECT_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]from Sofa[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SONGHAI_SOFA">
			<Text>Sofa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SONGHAI_SOFA_HELP">
			<Text>Ranged Unit excelling at supporting your cavalry. Only the Songhai may build it. All mounted units within two tiles receive a [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat boost. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Medic I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SONGHAI_SOFA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Sofa is a Songhai unique unit, replacing the Crossbowman. It serves as an excellent support unit starting with the Medic I promotion and a 15% Damage increase to all Mounted units within 2 tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SONGHAI_SOFA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Sofa is a Mandinka term for slave soldiers who served in the army of the various Empires of West Africa. Originally, the Sofas were horse grooms of the soldier-nobility, the Farari, but their role slowly changed to become skirmishers and soldiers in their own right. Sofas were recruited from "jonow" (slaves) captured in battle or bought from afar. The institution of slavery in the Mali and Songhai Empires heavily rewarded loyalty, and jonow could rise to civil or military positions of prominence. Jonow became part of their master's clan, and were often freed after a certain amount of years.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Sofas were equipped with two quivers, and their bow was small by European standards, so sofas employed deadly poisons and fired in arcs to give their arrows strength.
			</Text>
		</Row>		
		
		<!-- SPAD -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 11/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD">
			<Text>SPAD S.VII</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD_HELP">
			<Text>Potent Modern Era flying Unit. Only France may build it. Has a longer intercept range. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Air Logistics[ENDCOLOR] Promotion. Does not require [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]does not use Military Supply[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The SPAD S.VII is France's early air superiority fighter. These fighters will help create a strong French presence in the air with their ability to attack twice in a turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FRANCE_SPAD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				World War I saw rapid technological and tactical changes in how wars were fought, including the adoption of aircraft for scouting and bombing. These machines opened an entirely new theatre of war. Despite their promise, the first aircrafts were slow, clumsy, and unreliable due to their underpowered combustion engines. This all changed in 1915 when Marc Birgikt invented a new V8 engine boasting 150 horsepower and weighing only 330 pounds. The French high command saw the new motor's value as an aircraft engine and commissioned a new fighter aircraft: The Société Pour L'Aviation et ses Dérivés, or "SPAD" S. VII.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				By late 1916, SPAD VIIs were beginning to see action, and were widely adopted by allied pilots for the rest of the war. Though lacking the maneuverability of older Nieuport fighters, the SPAD VII was unmatched in sheer speed, travelling in excess of 127mph and capable of diving at more than 249mph. Pilots created entirely new tactics to leverage this speed, which gave the SPAD the ability to safely avoid pitched battles. The added stability in diving was especially appreciated over the old Nieuports, which had a bad habit of shedding their wings during maneuvers.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Air superiority became a constant arms race against newer and better German designs and engines. By the end of the war, the SPAD VII's single .303 Vickers machine gun was outmatched by German fighters, which carried at least two machine guns. The heavier and faster SPAD XIII eventually replaced the SPAD VII by late 1917, and saw France through the remainder of the War. Despite its shortcomings, the SPAD series is remembered as one of the fastest and most powerful of WWI fighters.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Standschützen -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUSTRIA_STANDSCHUTZEN">
			<Text>Schützenstand</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUSTRIA_STANDSCHUTZEN_TEXT">
			<Text>The Standschützen were originally rifle guilds and companies that had been formed in the 15th and 16th centuries within the Austrian county of Tyrol. A Standschütze was an enrolled member of a Schützenstand ("shooting club"), which automatically committed him to the voluntary military protection of the state of Tyrol and Vorarlberg. In effect this made Standschützen a Tyrolean local militia and home guard.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Standschützen were periodically called upon to defend their homeland from rebellions and invasions, but their actions in World War I were particularly distinguished. Italy entered late into the war against Austria and opened a new front through the Alpine passes of Tyrol. The Austrians had already committed battalions of Tyrolean recruits elsewhere upon the war's initial outbreak, so the Standschützen consisting of young, elderly, and injured men were called upon to defend their province with little notice or material support. Despite this, the Standschützen fought valiantly in defense of their homes and repulsed the Italians for weeks until regular troops could arrive. It is without a doubt that the actions of the Standschützen saved Autria a devastating loss against a fresh invasion by an opportunistic foe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUSTRIA_STANDSCHUTZEN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Standschützen is an Austrian unique building, replacing the Arsenal. It is cheaper than the Arsenal and available earlier. Increases the City's [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Bombardment Range by 1. It allows for faster construction of land military units in the city. It also provides additional yields for each city-state ally.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUSTRIA_STANDSCHUTZEN_HELP">
			<Text>Increases the City's [ICON_RANGE_STRENGTH] Ranged Strike Range by 1.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+10% [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Military Supply from Population. Garrisoned units receive an additional 5 Health when healing in this city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for each City-State Ally. +30% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and 15 XP for Gunpowder Units, and +15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to all other Land Military Units.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_CITY_STATE] Empire Size Modifier is reduced by 5% in this City.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Steam Mill -->
		<!-- Created by Gazebo -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL">
			<Text>Steam Mill</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_STEAM_MILL_TEXT">
			<Text>Stationary steam engines are fixed steam engines used for pumping or driving mills and factories, and for power generation. They are distinct from locomotive engines used on railways, traction engines for heavy steam haulage on roads, steam cars (and other motor vehicles), agricultural engines used for ploughing or threshing, marine engines, and the steam turbines used as the mechanism of power generation for most nuclear power plants. They were introduced during the 18th century and widely made for the whole of the 19th century and most of the first half of the 20th century, only declining as electricity supply and the internal combustion engine became more widespread.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every Steam Mill on Empire. Manufactories worked by the City gain +4 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]2 Specialists in this City no longer produce [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from Urbanization.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When you complete a building from the Industrial Era or later, gain 10% of its construction cost as Points towards a [ICON_GREAT_ENGINEER] Great Engineer.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to Engineer Specialists.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal: +3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique English replacement for the Factory. The Steam Mill is cheaper, requires no [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal, is available earlier than the Factory, and provides additional Production to [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal worked by the City. The Steam Mill also provides [ICON_GREAT_ENGINEER] Great Engineer points when constructing buildings, while increasing the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of engineer specialists. Since Steam Mills do not require Coal, you can use your Coal surplus to build Seaports and ironclads, or you can trade it away for a large amount of gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Qullqa & Coca -->	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INCA_QULLQA">
			<Text>Qullqa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INCA_QULLQA_HELP">
			<Text>Units stationed in this city heal [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]5 HP[ENDCOLOR] every turn, regardless of any actions taken. Excess [ICON_FOOD] Food in this City can never drop below 1.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+25 [ICON_FOOD] Food when completed. 15% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All [ICON_CONNECTED] City Connections produce +3% more [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Allows [ICON_FOOD] Food to be moved from this city along trade routes inside your civilization.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_WHEAT] Wheat: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_MAIZE] Maize: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_RICE] Rice: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE]Nearby [ICON_RES_BANANA] Bananas: +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INCA_QULLQA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Qullqa is the unique Granary replacement for the Inca. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Granary, the Qullqa heals your garrisoned units every turn. The Qullqa renders the city it is built in immune from [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Starvation[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Stagnation[ENDCOLOR]. It also increases the Gold you receive from City connections in your empire. Build Qullqas in all your cities to maximize the gold bonuses from your road connections, and to keep your populace safe and healthy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INCA_QULLQA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Qullqa were storage silos located along roadsides near cities and political centers across the Tawantinsuyu. The vast network of Qullqas stored food and supplies for the general populace and the military. This system acted as emergency reserves for the peasantry to protect against the frequent crop failures that took place in the precarious, high-altitude communities throughout the Inca's domains. The storehouses also relieved soldiers from the need to forage, but required constant maintenance from the local populace.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Maintaining and stocking the Qullqa system was the responsibility of local lords who resided in stations called Tambos, each located within a day's march of the next. Royal Qullqa stored the luxury and ceremonial goods of the Incan nobility, including feathers, precious stones, and Coca leaves. Coca production was jealously guarded as an imperial monopoly; cultivation and distribution of coca was strictly under the control of the nobles and a few favored classes. In fact, the entire economy of the Incan Empire functioned off a command economy, where access to and control of the goods stored in the Qullqa system ensured the wellbeing and continued expansion of the empire. 
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_COCA">
			<Text>Coca</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_COCA_TEXT">
			<Text>Coca is the leaf of any of four cultivated species of the family Erythroxylaceae native to western South America. The plant is famous for its various medicinal and nutritional uses, increasing alertness, dulling pain, supressing appetite, and treating altitude sickness. The leaves are traditionally chewed or brewed into a tea. Coca made an impression on the Spanish conquerors for its ability to help people work harder, even through exhaustion or hunger.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Today, coca is best known for its psychoactive alkaloid, cocaine. The alkaloid content of coca leaves is relatively low, requiring a large number of leaves for a single batch of cocaine. Coca leaf extract was once used widely in a wide range of medicinal and consumer products, but was later made a controlled substance and eliminated from North American and European consumer markets in the early 20th century.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_COCA">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus: [ENDCOLOR]Grants [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Coca Leaves[ENDCOLOR] Promotion to all Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INCA_COCA">
			<Text>Coca Leaves</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_INCA_COCA_HELP">
			<Text>Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]can cross Mountains[ENDCOLOR]. +15% [ICON_WORKER] Work Rate.</Text>
		</Row>
			
		<!-- Tarkhan -->		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_MIGRATION">
			<Text>Migration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_MIGRATION_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_ARROW_RIGHT] Movement Point to Workers and Settlers [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]that begin the turn stacked with this unit[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_SACKER">
			<Text>Bellum Alet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_HUNS_SACKER_HELP">
			<Text>15 HP to all adjacent Friendly Units [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Pillage[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HUNS_TARKHAN">
			<Text>Tarkhan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HUNS_TARKHAN_HELP">
			<Text>Mounted warrior who supports Civilian and other Units with its unique abilities. Only the Huns may build it. Does not require [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses. +1 Movement to [ICON_TEAM_1] Settlers and [ICON_WORKER] Workers that begin the turn stacked with the Tarkhan. Whenever this unit pillages a tile, adjacent friendly units are also healed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HUNS_TARKHAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Tarkhan is the Hunnic unique replacement for the Horseman. The Tarkhan can help to quickly spread your empire by increasing the movement of Settlers and Workers. Pillaging tiles with a Tarkhan heals all your adjacent units, which can be handy for healing a recently captured unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HUNS_TARKHAN_TEXT">
			<Text>Tarkhan were nobles and high-ranking commanders within the armies of the Xiongnu and Hunnic empires. The term spread throughout the languages and peoples of the steppes, appearing as a title within Turkic, Mongol and Iranian cultures, even becoming a common boys name. Analogous to modern day commanders, the Tarkhan were the protectors and conquerors of the Hunnic empire, spurring their civilization forward to greatness.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Telpochcalli -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_TELPOCHCALLI">
			<Text>Telpochcalli</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_TELPOCHCALLI_TEXT">
			<Text>The Telpochcalli, meaning "House of the Young Men" were centers of education for Aztec youth. While the children of nobles went to a separate institution called the Calmecac, the Telpochcalli were open to all Aztec boys starting at age 15, making them one of the earliest examples of public education in history. Education in Aztec society focused on civics, warfare, and religion. Accounts of the experience of growing up going to a Telpochcalli describe an austere and strict environment, where boys were expected to grow their own food on collective farms and were given responsibilities such as maintaining and repairing public facilities like temples.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_TELPOCHCALLI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Telpochcalli is an Aztec unique building, replacing the Library. In addition to the regular bonuses of the Library, the Telpochcalli provides additional science that scales with population. Whenever you trigger a Golden Age, the yields and experience given by the Telpochcalli are increased. This bonus does not scale retroactively, so make sure you build Telpochcalli in your cities as quickly as possible so you can start earning rewards.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZTEC_TELPOCHCALLI_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 4 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City. Permanently gains +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, and +2 Experience to all newly trained Units in this city whenever you enter a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age, stacking up to 10 times. This bonus is not retroactive.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]-1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_RESEARCH] Illiteracy. 1 Specialist in this City no longer produces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_URBANIZATION] Urbanization.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Tersane -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 1/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OTTOMAN_TERSANE">
			<Text>Tersane</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OTTOMAN_TERSANE_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Ottoman Great Person Tile Improvement. Can be built by Expending a [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral or embarked [ICON_GREAT_GENERAL] Great General. Must be built in water next to a City, but not next to another Tersane.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points. +25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +15 Experience for Naval Units built in the Adjacent City. Does not stack with multiple Tersane next to the same City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building a Tersane claims adjacent tiles. Units standing on a Tersane receive +50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Tile Defense. Deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OTTOMAN_TERSANE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Turkish word 'Tersane' is derived from the Venetian 'darsane', from which the English word 'arsenal' is also derived. Though never at the forefront of shipbuilding technology, the Ottomans enjoyed over a century of naval dominance in the Mediterranean following their conquest of Constantinople in 1453. The largest Tersane, constructed at the Golden Horn across from Constantinople, housed over 160 docks, drydocks, storehouses and supply depots, making it one of the largest centers of commerce and industry in the Mediterranean.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Ottoman naval power was maintained through its tremendous shipbuilding capacity and its allegiances to the Barbary corsairs of North Africa. This pre-eminence was finally ended at the battle of Lepanto, where a combined Spanish and Venetian armada delivered a crushing defeat to the Ottomans, capturing or destroying more than two thirds of the Ottoman navy. In response, the Ottomans built 250 new vessels within six months.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"You come to see how we bear our misfortune. But I would have you know the difference between your loss and ours. In wresting Cyprus from you, we deprived you of an arm; in defeating our fleet, you have only shaved our beard."[NEWLINE] Grand Vizier Mehmed Sokullu, on the defeat at Lepanto, and the capture of Cyprus, which the Ottomans had taken earlier the same year[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Can be built by Expending a Great Admiral or embarked Great General. Must be built in water next to a City, but not next to another Tersane.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points. +25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +15 Experience for Naval Units built in the Adjacent City. Does not stack with multiple Tersane next to the same City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building a Tersane claims adjacent tiles. Units standing on a Tersane receive +50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Tile Defense. Deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_OTTOMAN_TERSANE">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_OTTOMAN_TERSANE]Tersane[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_OTTOMAN_TERSANE_HELP">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points. Increases the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production rate and Experience of new Naval Units in an adjacent City. Gives [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it. Claims adjacent tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_OTTOMAN_TERSANE_REC">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed.[NEWLINE]Unique Ottoman Tile Improvement. Provides [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science. Gives a [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Teutonic Order -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_TEUTONIC_ORDER">
			<Text>Teutonic Order</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_TEUTONIC_ORDER_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Order of Brothers of the German House of Saint Mary in Jerusalem, more commonly known as the Teutonic Order, is a Catholic knightly order christened in 1190 in Acre, Jerusalem. Originally founded as an adjunct of the Knights Hospitaller, the Order was tasked with establishing hospitals and helping Germanic pilgrims on their way to the Holy Land. Within 50 years, the German Catholic order became a state unto itself, prosecuting a holy crusade against Baltic pagans from their capital in present day Malbork, Poland.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] 
				After Christian forces were expelled from Jerusalem, the Teutonic knights found work as mercenaries and guardsmen in Transylvania, Hungary, and then Poland, before becoming the largest player in a new Prussian Crusade against the pagan inhabitants of the Eastern Baltics. The Teutonic Order carried out a bloody, centuries-long campaign of forced conversions and ethnic replacement that brought them into conflict with Estonians, Lithuanians, Old Prussians and their former Polish allies. Resistance to forced Christianization by Catholic knights would shape the national identities of all these neighboring peoples.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The adoption of Christianity in Lithuania along with Poland's attempts to politically isolate the Teutonic Order from the rest of Catholicism left the Order without a purpose (and a shortage of friends) by 1520. In response, the Grand Master of the Order, Albert of Brandenburg, resigned from the Order, converted to Lutheranism, and styled himself Duke of Prussia. With the consent of the Order, Albert converted their land holdings into a secularized fiefdom, making Prussia the first Protestant state. Though declining in political force, the Teutonic Order continued to exist as a Catholic state through its holdings in Germania until forcibly dissolved by Napoleon Bonaparte in 1809. The Teutonic Order eventually reformed and still exists today as a ceremonial and charitable organization.  
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_TEUTONIC_ORDER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Teutonic Order is Germany's unique wonder, replacing the Heroic Epic. This wonder provides strong bonuses to all cities in your empire with a Barracks comparable to that of a full Order. All new units trained in any city with a Barracks receive the Morale promotion for free.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]With this wonder, Germany is able to found and reform much more easilly and quickly than other civilizations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GERMANY_TEUTONIC_ORDER_HELP">
			<Text>
				Does not require a Barracks. Grants a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] Barracks in the City. A [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] Great Writer appears near the city. Contains 1 slot for a [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work of Writing.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Castles gain +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and all Barracks in the Empire gain +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +3 [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense, and +50 HP. Units trained in a City with a Barracks gain the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Morale[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]15 [ICON_PEACE] Faith whenever you kill an enemy Unit, scaling with Era. Enables you to select a Reformation Belief at 5% below its normal Global [ICON_RELIGION] Follower requirement (20% on Standard).
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Tophet -->
		<!-- Created by pineappledan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARTHAGE_TOPHET">
			<Text>Tophet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARTHAGE_TOPHET_HELP">
			<Text>Gain +20 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in the City whenever a Unit is purchased, scaling with Era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARTHAGE_TOPHET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Tophet is the unique Shrine replacement for Carthage. In addition to the normal bonuses of a Shrine, the Tophet provides Culture whenever a unit is purchased in the City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARTHAGE_TOPHET_TEXT">
			<Text>"Tophet" is a Hebrew term for a place of worship and human sacrifice to the Canaanite gods, and has become a colorful synonym for hell within Judeo-Christian theology. Usually located outside cities, Tophets were holy places where sacrifices could be presented to gods of the Phoenician pantheon.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Regular sacrifices were made to ensure the prosperity of Carthage and the ashes of burnt offerings were sealed within the Tophet. Child sacrifice, once prevalent throughout the Near-East, was a persistent hallmark of Carthaginian religious life long after contemporary cultures had shunned the practice. Modern archaeological evidence suggests children were sacrificed in times of great stress such as wars, plagues, and natural disasters as an act of divine supplication.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Ulticur -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUNS_ALTI_CUR">
			<Text>Ulticur</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUNS_ALTI_CUR_HELP">
			<Text>Gain +25 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science as an instant boost whenever a Building is constructed in City, scaling with Era. Provides 2 [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Stables gain +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_GOLD] in this City for every City-State that you can demand Tribute from. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Does not require any prerequisite building. +2 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Global Happiness and [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Military Supply for every Civilization you are at War with. The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUNS_ALTI_CUR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Ulticur is the Hunnic Unique Wonder, replacing the Ironworks. In addition to the normal bonuses of the Ironworks, the Ulticur increases Science and Culture, and boosts Culture and Production from all Stables on empire. The wonder provides additional Gold and Happiness from demanding tribute from minor City-States.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUNS_ALTI_CUR_TEXT">
			<Text>The Huns' origins remain shrouded in mystery, but one clue to their Xiongnu heritage is their rule by an Ulticur, or "Six-Horns Council". The Ulticur was a small council of nobles, the most powerful men within the Hunnic Empire besides the emperor himself. Each was seated according to their standing with the emperor, with the emperor's favorite seated to his immediate right.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			An emperor's legitimacy depended heavily on the tributes he could extract from the surrounding kingdoms and distribute to his nobles. It is surmised that insufficient tributes from the Chinese and other client tribes triggered the decline and disappearance of the Xiongnu in East Asia, only for them reappear as the Huns of Eastern Europe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALERT_ALTI_CUR_MINOR_TRIBUTE">
			<Text>
				Demanding tribute from the city-state has earned you {1_Num} [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +6 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness for 20 turns!
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAYER_EVENT_CHOICE_ALTI_CUR_HAPPINESS">
			<Text>Ulticur tribute bonus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PLAYER_EVENT_CHOICE_ALTI_CUR_HAPPINESS_HELP">
			<Text>+6 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness for 20 turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- University of Coimbra -->
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PORTUGAL_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA">
			<Text>University of Coimbra</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PORTUGAL_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_TEXT">
			<Text>Opened in 1290, the University of Coimbra is one of the oldest centers of higher learning in the world. The university was founded by King Dinis as the Lisbon Estudo Geral, originally with faculties of Arts, Law, Canon Law and Medicine. As the first and only university in Portugal for 350 years, the University of Coimbra became a focus of educational, political, and social influence in Portugal.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PORTUGAL_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Universiy of Coimbra is the unique Portuguese replacement for the Oxford University. It does not require a University, and provides a free University in the city. In addition to the normal bonuses of the Oxford University, it gives all naval units the ability to gain gold from exploration. With the University of Coimbra built, all Great Admirals gain the ability to restore all movement to all your Naval Units when expended. Use this ability in tandem with your Age of Discovery bonus to map the world out, and gain an upper hand in maneuvering around enemy ships.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PORTUGAL_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_HELP">
			<Text>Does not require a University in the City. Provides a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Free[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GREAT_SCIENTIST] Great Scientist and a University on Completion. All Universities gain +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. +50 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture every time you research a Technology, scaling with Era. -1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Unhappiness from [ICON_RESEARCH] Illiteracy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All Naval Units gain the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Age of Discovery[ENDCOLOR] Promotion. Whenever you Expend a [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral, all Naval Units on Empire have their full movement restored.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contains 2 slots for [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works of Writing. +3 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science when themed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost and [ICON_CITIZEN] Population Requirements increase based on the number of Cities you own.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PORTUGAL_AGE_OF_DISCOVERY">
			<Text>Age of Discovery</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_PORTUGAL_AGE_OF_DISCOVERY_HELP">
			<Text>Gain [ICON_GOLD] Gold [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]for revealing new areas[ENDCOLOR] on the map.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Vaka Nui --> 
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_VAKANUI">
			<Text>Vaka Nui</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_VAKANUI_HELP">
			<Text>Naval exploration unit. Only Polynesia may build it. Can heal outside friendly territory. Gains experience when revealing new tiles and [ICON_GOLD] Gold when attacking cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_VAKANUI_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Vaka Nui is a Polynesian unique unit, replacing the Trireme. The Vaka Nui gain experience from revealing unexplored regions of the map, and generates gold whenever it attacks cities. Explore uncharted waters with the Vaka Nui to gain a highly-trained navy with which to expand your empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_POLYNESIA_VAKANUI_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The distinctive twin-hulled catamarans developed by the Austronesian people are perhaps the earliest examples of open-ocean vessels. These exceptionally stable craft enabled Polynesians to explore and settle islands across the Pacific Ocean. Catamaran designs have had a resurgence in modern times because of their many advantages over single-hulled ship designs. This revitalization of catamarans has also renewed interest in Polynesian navigation and shipbuilding, with numerous recreations of traditional Polynesian craft being built for both cultural and research purposes.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Villa -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 10/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM">
			<Text>Villa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_HELP">
			<Text>Cannot be built on Resources or adjacent to a City or another Villa. Cannot be removed once it is built.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]On construction, immediately spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource on a tile adjacent to the Villa, and claims that tile if not already owned by Rome.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides additional [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on the tile, and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food in the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital [NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to adjacent Plantations.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to adjacent Farms.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_TEXT">
			<Text>Villae were country homes of upper class roman citizens. Over the progressive conquests and expansion of Roman territories and wealth, the villa evolved from relatively simple getaways for social elites into extravagant centers of sprawling agricultural landholdings called Latifundia, an ancient precursor to today’s agribusinesses. The first latifundia were created from land confiscated from conquered peoples in the early 2nd century BC in Magna Graecia (Southern Italy). The Latifundia system expanded with later conquests into Spain and North Africa.
			[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]These estates depended on forced labor for their productivity, often supplied by the enslavement of the same people who occupied the land before conquest. The Latifundia consolidated agricultural production into larger estates with greater economies of scale; owners re-invested profits by purchasing small neighbouring farms to increase their own holdings. Evicted from their farms and replaced by slave labour, the Roman peasantry were forced to find work in the cities of Rome, though often resorting to squatting and handouts.
			[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Latifundia became the template upon which later European nations would base their imperial experiments. The Spanish are especially noteworthy for patterning the Encomienda system after the late Roman Latifundia.
			[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Cannot be built on Resources or adjacent to a City or another Villa. Cannot be removed once it is built.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]On construction, immediately spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource on a tile adjacent to the Villa, and claims that tile if not already owned by Rome.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides additional [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on the tile, and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food in the Capital [NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to adjacent Plantations.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to adjacent Farms.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM]Villa[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Villa, which yields [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on the tile and gives [ICON_FOOD] Food permanently in the [ICON_CAPITOL] Capital.[NEWLINE]On construction, spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource adjacent to the Latifundium, and the Figs tile is claimed by Rome.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Plantations Receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Farms Receive +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ROME_LATIFUNDIUM_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Spawns an Improved [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource adjacent to the Latifundium on construction, and the Figs tile is claimed by Rome.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Plantations Receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Farms Receive +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Xiafan Guanjun -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINA_XIAFAN_GUANJUN">
			<Text>Baochuan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINA_XIAFAN_GUANJUN_HELP">
			<Text>Hulking Renaissance Era Naval Ranged Unit. Only China may build it. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Hull III[ENDCOLOR] promotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Generates [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence every turn when stationed in a City-State's borders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINA_XIAFAN_GUANJUN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Baochuan is a Chinese unique unit. It is much sturdier than the Frigate it replaces, and is available earlier. You can use your Xiafan Guanjun to passively bring city-states under your sway, or take advantage of its bonus against cities and dominate coastal empires.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHINA_XIAFAN_GUANJUN_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Xiafan Guanjun (lit. "The Foreign Expeditionary Armada") was the great treasure fleet of the Ming Dynasty. At the behest of Emperor Zhu Di, the legendary admiral Zheng He headed seven voyages between 1405 and 1433 AD. The Xiafan Guanjun ranged as far as the Arabian Peninsula in their task of projecting Chinese influence abroad, bringing many smaller nations under the suzerainty of China.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Xiafan Guanjun had some of the largest wooden ships ever constructed, called Baochuan, measuring up to 416 feet in length. It would be another century before European ships could match the size and power of China’s fleet, making China the undisputed naval superpower of the 15th century. Despite their superiority, Zheng He’s voyages were primarily diplomatic, bringing envoys and even kings before the emperor to present tribute and perform the 'kowtow', a ritual act of reverence and subservience.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				"As an engine for carrying man and his commerce upon the high and stormy seas as well as on the vast inland waterways, it is doubtful if any class of vessel… is more suited or better adapted to its purpose than the Chinese or Indian junk, and it is certain that for flatness of sail and handiness, the Chinese rig is unsurpassed."[NEWLINE]-H. Warington Smyth
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CHINA_KOWTOW">
			<Text>Kowtow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_CHINA_KOWTOW_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence per turn [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]inside City-State Territory[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]Maximum Hit Points increased by 25.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Created by Blue Ghost-->

		<!-- Yamato -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO">
			<Text>Yamato</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO_HELP">
		<Text>Powerful Naval Ranged Unit. Only Japan may build it. Has more range, power and higher defense than the Battleship it replaces. Earns [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points when killing Naval Units.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Receive +600 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points whenever a Yamato is constructed.[NEWLINE]Enemies receive +400 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +400 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points whenever they destroy a Yamato.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Yamato is the unique Battleship replacement for Japan which is significantly more powerful. It has increased range, attack, strength, defense against attack and earns Great Admiral Points on kills. Use them to dominate the seas in the end game, giving you the edge for a Domination Victory.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
			Each Yamato gives points towards a Golden Age when constructed, but sinking a Yamato rewards enemies with Golden Age points and Culture, so don't leave your Yamatos without an escort.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO_TEXT">
			<Text>The Yamato-class battleships were the crown jewel of the Imperial Japanese Navy during World War II. Displacing 73,000 tonnes at full load, they were the heaviest and most powerfully armed battleships ever constructed. Each Yamato carried nine 18.1 inch guns, the largest naval artillery ever fitted to a warship, each capable of firing 3,000 lb. shells over 26 miles. Two battleships of the class, Yamato and Musashi, were completed while a third, Shinano, was converted to an aircraft carrier during construction. All were sunk by American forces during WWII.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Due to their size, speed, and power, The Yamato-class visibly embodied Japan's determination and readiness to defend its interests against the western powers, especially the United States. One of the reasons that the warship may have such significance in Japanese culture is that the word "Yamato" was often used as a poetic name for Japan itself. Thus, the construction and destruction of the Yamato battleships became symbolic for the rise and fall of Japanese imperial aspirations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO">
			<Text>Taikan Kyohosyugi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_JAPAN_YAMATO_HELP">
			<Text>Earn [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points when [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]killing Naval Units[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Yassa Court -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo 29/10/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_WONDER">
			<Text>Adopt the Yassa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT">
			<Text>The Yassa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_HELP">
			<Text>Upon completion provides a FREE copy of [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]The Yassa[ENDCOLOR] in all owned cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production towards Ranged, Siege, Mounted and Armor Units. +10 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, [ICON_CULTURE]Culture, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every City on Empire whenever you Conquer a City, scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]All [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Needs thresholds are slightly reduced in all Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Mongolian national wonder. Once completed, a copy of the Yassa appears in all Cities. The Yassa slightly reduces all global needs and Empire size modifiers for each city in your empire and increases production of all Land-based military units, except Unmounted Melee. Conquering Cities triggers a small amount of Gold, Science and Culture in every city. With the Yassa providing stacking global unhappiness reduction in each city, expand and conquer at will without concern for your citizens' needs.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONGOLIA_YASSA_COURT_TEXT">
			<Text>Yassa was a secret written code of law created by Genghis Khan. The word Yassa translates into "order" or "decree". It was the de facto law of the Mongol Empire even though the "law" was never actually made public. The Yassa seems to have originated from decrees issued in wartime, and was later codified and expanded to include cultural and life-style conventions. By keeping the Yassa secret, the decrees could be modified and used selectively. It is believed that the Yassa was supervised by Genghis Khan himself with the help of the high judge of the Mongol Empire: His stepbrother, Shihihutag. Genghis Khan appointed his second son Chagatai (a.k.a. Chagatai Khan) to oversee the execution of the laws.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Yellow Brow -->
		<!-- Created by adan_eslavo on 3/11/2017 -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE">
			<Text>Big Horse Dance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE_HELP">
			<Text>Adds [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]on Fortifying[ENDCOLOR]. Is stronger when damaged.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE_PERFORMED">
			<Text>Big Horse Dance Performed</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_UNIT_SHOSHONE_BIG_HORSE_DANCE_PERFORMED_HELP">
			<Text>Unit [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]is Fortified[ENDCOLOR]. [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus added.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW">
			<Text>Yellow Brow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW_HELP">
			<Text>Tenacious Renaissance Era Unit. Only the Shoshone may build it. Has the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Formation I[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, gains [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength when damaged, and a double [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat bonus from fortifying.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Yellow Brow is unmatched for its ability to hold ground. Never one to retreat, the Yellow brow fights at full strength regardless of health, and has double the normal bonus from fortifying. This unit is very effective against enemy cavalry</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SHOSHONE_YELLOW_BROW_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Yellow Brows (Sh. Ohamupe) were one of two military societies within the Shoshone, playing an integral role in hunting, scouting, and policing within their bands. Yellow Brow braves shaved their heads into a cockscomb 'mohawk', and painted their exposed heads yellow, hence their common English name.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The Yellow Brows were composed of only the bravest and most daring of the young men, tasked with keeping order on hunting expeditions, scouting, and soldiering. The Society never had more than a few hundred members at a time; members elected their replacement upon graduation. A young Yellow Brow was expected to act and speak in a contrarian way as a sign of membership.  For instance, when asked if he would like to join the Yellow Brows, it was expected that the young man would say 'No' as a sign of willingness to join, or 'Yes' if he wished to decline.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				In battle, Yellow Brows were led by a war chief who carried a long cane tipped with a stone or metal dagger.  The cane was used to grab and unhorse opponents, or as a No-Retreat signal. If the enemy was gaining the upper hand, the chief would drive his staff into the ground and the braves would defend him to the last. Yellow Brows were banned from leaving their chief's side until another member of the tribe came and released the braves from their charge. Deserting the chief was met with abject mockery, and often resulted in banishment from the tribe.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>
