<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 12/21/2019 7:14:48 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!--City state luxuries-->
		<!--Beer-->
		<!--<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_BEER">
			<Text>Beer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_BEER_HELP">
			<Text>Beers are only available through a Mercantile City-State.[NEWLINE]
			
			[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +6 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness added to Empire-Wide Luxury value.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_BEER_TEXT">
			<Text>Beer is one of the oldest and most widely consumed alcoholic drinks in the world. It is also the third most popular drink overall after water and tea. Beer is brewed from cereal grains—most commonly from malted barley, though wheat, maize (corn), and rice are also used. During the brewing process, fermentation of the starch sugars in the wort produces ethanol and carbonation in the resulting beer.</Text>
		</Row>-->
		<!--Bird's Nest-->
		<!--<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_BIRDS_NEST">
			<Text>Bird's Nest</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_BIRDS_NEST_HELP">
			<Text>Bird's Nests are only available through a Mercantile City-State.[NEWLINE]
			
			[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_GOLD] Gold in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_BIRDS_NEST_TEXT">
			<Text>Edible bird's nests are bird nests created by edible-nest swiftlets, Indian swiftlets, and other swiftlets using solidified saliva, which are harvested for human consumption. They are particularly prized in Chinese culture due to their rarity, supposedly high nutritional value, and flavour. Edible bird's nests are among the most expensive animal products consumed by humans, with nests being sold at prices up to about $3,000 per pound ($6,600/kg), depending on grading.</Text>
		</Row>-->
		<!--Champagne-->
		<!--<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_CHAMPAGNE">
			<Text>Champagne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_CHAMPAGNE_HELP">
			<Text>Champagne is only available through a Mercantile City-State.[NEWLINE]
			
			[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_CHAMPAGNE_TEXT">
			<Text>Champagne is a French sparkling wine. Many people use the term Champagne as a generic term for sparkling wine, but in the EU and some other countries, it is illegal to label any product Champagne unless it comes from the Champagne region of France and is produced under the rules of the appellation.</Text>
		</Row>-->
		<!--Cheese-->
		<!--<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_CHEESE">
			<Text>Cheese</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_CHEESE_HELP">
			<Text>Cheese is only available through a Mercantile City-State.[NEWLINE]
			
			[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_CHEESE_TEXT">
			<Text>Cheese is a dairy product derived from milk that is produced in a wide range of flavors, textures, and forms by coagulation of the milk protein casein. Over a thousand types of cheese from various countries are produced. Their styles, textures and flavors depend on the origin of the milk (including the animal's diet), whether they have been pasteurized, the butterfat content, the bacteria and mold, the processing, and aging. Cheese is valued for its portability, long life, and high content of fat, protein, calcium, and phosphorus.</Text>
		</Row>-->
		<!--Honey-->
		<!--<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_HONEY">
			<Text>Honey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_HONEY_HELP">
			<Text>Honey is only available through a Mercantile City-State.[NEWLINE]
			
			[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_HONEY_TEXT">
			<Text>Honey is a sweet, viscous food substance made by bees and some related insects. Bees produce honey from the sugary secretions of plants (floral nectar) or from secretions of other insects (such as honeydew), by regurgitation, enzymatic activity, and water evaporation. Bees store honey in wax structures called honeycombs. Honey use and production have a long and varied history as an ancient activity. Several cave paintings in Cuevas de la Araña in Spain depict humans foraging for honey at least 8,000 years ago.</Text>
		</Row>-->
		<!--Manuscripts-->
		<!--<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MANUSCRIPTS">
			<Text>Manuscripts</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MANUSCRIPTS_HELP">
			<Text>Manuscripts are only available through a Mercantile City-State.[NEWLINE]
			
			[NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +20% [ICON_PEACE] Faith in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_MANUSCRIPTS_TEXT">
			<Text>A Manuscript or Handwrit is written information that has been manually created by one or more people, such as a hand-written letter, as opposed to being printed or reproduced some other way. The term may also be used for information that is hand-recorded in other ways than writing, for example inscriptions that are chiselled upon a hard material or scratched (the original meaning of graffiti) as with a knife point in plaster or with a stylus on a waxed tablet (the way Romans made notes), or are in cuneiform writing, impressed with a pointed stylus in a flat tablet of unbaked clay.</Text>
		</Row>-->
		<!--Luxuries-->
		<!--Lavender-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_LAVENDER">
			<Text>Lavender</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_LAVENDER_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_LAVENDER_TEXT">
			<Text>Lavender is a genus of 47 known species of flowering plants in the mint family, Lamiaceae. It is native to the Old World and is found from Cape Verde and the Canary Islands, Europe across to northern and eastern Africa, the Mediterranean, southwest Asia to southeast India. Many members of the genus are cultivated extensively in temperate climates as ornamental plants for garden and landscape use, for use as culinary herbs, and also commercially for the extraction of essential oils.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Obsidian-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_OBSIDIAN">
			<Text>Obsidian</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_OBSIDIAN_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength when attacking.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_OBSIDIAN_TEXT">
			<Text>Obsidian is a naturally occurring volcanic glass formed as an extrusive igneous rock. It was an important part of the material culture of Pre-Columbian Mesoamerica. Obsidian was a highly integrated part of daily and ritual life, and its widespread and varied use may be a significant contributor to Mesoamerica's lack of metallurgy. Most notably, it was used to make macuahuitl, a wooden club with obsidian blades.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Platinum-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_PLATINUM">
			<Text>Platinum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_PLATINUM_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_RESEARCH] Science in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_PLATINUM_TEXT">
			<Text>Platinum is a chemical element and a precious metal which is remarkably resistant to corrosion. Consequently, platinum is often found chemically uncombined as native platinum. Because it occurs naturally in the alluvial sands of various rivers, it was first used by pre-Columbian South American natives to produce artifacts. Platinum is used in catalytic converters, laboratory equipment, electrical contacts and electrodes, platinum resistance thermometers, dentistry equipment, and jewelry.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Poppy-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_POPPY">
			<Text>Poppy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_POPPY_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +25% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person generation in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_POPPY_TEXT">
			<Text>A poppy is a flowering plant in the subfamily Papaveroideae of the family Papaveraceae. Poppies are herbaceous plants, often grown for their colourful flowers. One species of poppy, Papaver somniferum, is the source of the narcotic drug opium which contains powerful medicinal alkaloids such as morphine and has been used since ancient times as an analgesic and narcotic medicinal and recreational drug. It also produces edible seeds. Following the trench warfare in the poppy fields of Flanders, Belgium during World War I, poppies have become a symbol of remembrance of soldiers who have died during wartime.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Tin-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_TIN">
			<Text>Tin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_TIN_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_TIN_TEXT">
			<Text>Tin is a silvery metal that characteristically has a faint yellow hue. The first tin alloy used on a large scale was bronze, made of 1/8 tin and 7/8 copper, from as early as 3000 BC. After 600 BC, pure metallic tin was produced. Pewter, which is an alloy of 85–90% tin with the remainder commonly consisting of copper, antimony, and lead, was used for flatware from the Bronze Age until the 20th century. In modern times, tin is used in many alloys, most notably tin/lead soft solders, which are typically 60% or more tin, and in the manufacture of transparent, electrically conducting films of indium tin oxide in optoelectronic applications. Another large application for tin is corrosion-resistant tin plating of steel. Because of the low toxicity of inorganic tin, tin-plated steel is widely used for food packaging as tin cans.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Bonus-->
		<!--Coconut-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_COCONUT">
			<Text>Coconut</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_COCONUT_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_COCONUT_TEXT">
			<Text>Coconuts are known for their versatility of uses, ranging from food to cosmetics. The inner flesh of the mature seed, as well as the coconut milk extracted from it, forms a regular part of the diets of many people in the tropics and subtropics. The hard shells, fibrous husks and long pinnate leaves can be used as material to make a variety of products for furnishing and decorating. The coconut also has cultural and religious significance in certain societies, particularly in India, where it is used in Hindu rituals.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Hardwood-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_HARDWOOD">
			<Text>Hardwood</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_HARDWOOD_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Local City Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] -20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost of pre-Industrial Naval Melee Units and Naval Ranged Units, and pre-Renaissance Siege Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_HARDWOOD_TEXT">
			<Text>Hardwood is wood from dicot trees. These are usually found in broad-leaved temperate and tropical forests. In temperate and boreal latitudes they are mostly deciduous, but in tropics and subtropics mostly evergreen. As the name suggests, the wood from these trees is generally harder than that of softwoods, but there are significant exceptions. Hardwoods are employed in a large range of applications, including fuel, tools, construction, boat building, furniture making, musical instruments, flooring, cooking, barrels, and manufacture of charcoal.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Lead-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_LEAD">
			<Text>Lead</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_LEAD_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Local City Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] -10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost of Ancient and Classical Buildings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_LEAD_TEXT">
			<Text>Lead is a heavy metal that is denser than most common materials. Lead is soft and malleable, and also has a relatively low melting point. Lead is easily extracted from its ores; prehistoric people in Western Asia knew of it. Galena, a principal ore of lead, often bears silver, interest in which helped initiate widespread extraction and use of lead in ancient Rome. Lead production declined after the fall of Rome and did not reach comparable levels until the Industrial Revolution.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Pineapple-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_PINEAPPLE">
			<Text>Pineapple</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_PINEAPPLE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_PINEAPPLE_TEXT">
			<Text>The pineapple is a tropical plant with an edible fruit, also called a pineapple, and the most economically significant plant in the family Bromeliaceae. The pineapple is indigenous to South America where it has been cultivated for many centuries. The introduction of the pineapple cultivation to Europe in the 17th century made it a significant cultural icon of luxury. Since the 1820s pineapple has been commercially grown in greenhouses and many troplcal plantations and it is the third most important tropical fruit in world production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Potato-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_POTATO">
			<Text>Potato</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_POTATO_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_POTATO_TEXT">
			<Text>The potato is a root vegetable native to the Americas. It was first domesticated in the region of modern-day southern Peru and northwestern Bolivia between 8000 and 5000 BC, where it was a staple food for the Inca Empire, as well as most Pre-Columbian Mapuches. It arrived in Europe sometime before the end of the 16th century by two different ports of entry: the first in Spain around 1570, and the second via the British Isles between 1588 and 1593. It had widely replaced the turnip and rutabaga by the 19th century. The crop slowly spread across Europe, becoming a major staple by mid-century, especially in Ireland.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Rubber-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_RUBBER">
			<Text>Rubber</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_RUBBER_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Local City Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] -20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost of Civilian Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_RUBBER_TEXT">
			<Text>Rubber was first used by the indigenous cultures of Mesoamerica. The earliest archeological evidence of the use of natural latex from the Hevea tree comes from the Olmec culture, in which rubber was first used for making balls for the Mesoamerican ballgame. Rubber was later used by the Maya and Aztec cultures – in addition to making balls Aztecs used rubber for other purposes such as making containers and to make textiles waterproof by impregnating them with the latex sap. Natural rubber is used extensively in many applications and products, either alone or in combination with other materials. In most of its useful forms, it has a large stretch ratio and high resilience, and is extremely waterproof.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Sulfur-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_SULFUR">
			<Text>Sulfur</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_SULFUR_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Local City Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] -20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost of post-Medieval Gun Units and Siege Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_SULFUR_TEXT">
			<Text>Sulfur is the tenth most common element by mass in the universe, and the fifth most common on Earth. Though sometimes found in pure, native form, sulfur on Earth usually occurs as sulfide and sulfate minerals. Being abundant in native form, sulfur was known in ancient times, being mentioned for its uses in ancient India, ancient Greece, China, and Egypt. A Song dynasty military treatise of 1044 AD described various formulas for Chinese black powder, which is a mixture of potassium nitrate, charcoal, and sulfur. It remains an ingredient of black gunpowder.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Titanium-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_TITANIUM">
			<Text>Titanium</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_TITANIUM_HELP">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Local City Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] -20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production Cost of post-Modern Fighter Units and Bomber Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_TITANIUM_TEXT">
			<Text>Titanium is a lustrous transition metal with a silver color, low density, and high strength. Titanium is resistant to corrosion in sea water, aqua regia, and chlorine. Titanium was discovered in Cornwall, Great Britain, by William Gregor in 1791 and was named by Martin Heinrich Klaproth after the Titans of Greek mythology. Titanium can be alloyed with iron, aluminium, vanadium, and molybdenum, among other elements, to produce strong, lightweight alloys for aerospace, military, industrial processes, and other applications. In its unalloyed condition, titanium is as strong as some steels, but less dense.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>